-DOCSTART- O

" O
Europe B-LOC_DEST
innovates O
three O
times O
as O
much O
as O
the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
in O
healthcare O
technologies O
per O
million O
inhabitants O
, O
but O
European O
companies O
get O
nine O
times O
less O
investment O
. O
" O
https://t.co/gafgz7yQRD O
Title O
: O
Lauxera B-ORG_ORIG
Capital I-ORG_ORIG
Partners I-ORG_ORIG
launches O
€ B-MONEY
100 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
fund O
for O
European O
healthcare O
startups O
Description O
: O
The O
French O
fund O
Lauxera B-ORG_ORIG
Capital I-ORG_ORIG
Partners I-ORG_ORIG
, O
which O
was O
launched O
last O
year O
in O
Paris B-LOC
and O
San B-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
, O
announces O
a O
€ B-MONEY
100 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
fund O
to O
support O
European O
healthtech O
startups O
. O
While O
the O
current O
pandemic O
has O
increased O
investor O
interest O
in O
digital O
technology O
, O
particularly O
teleworking O
and O
teleconferencing O

Major B-ORG_ORIG
Thai I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
Creates O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
Fund O
for O
Investments O
in O
Defi B-ORG_DEST
Siam I-ORG_DEST
Commercial I-ORG_DEST
Bank I-ORG_DEST
, O
Thailand B-LOC_DEST
’ O
s O
oldest O
bank O
, O
is O
cementing O
its O
reputation O
as O
a O
strong O
funder O
of O
… O
https://t.co/OcL2zXTt9a O
#Binance O
#BitcoinCash O
#Bitcoin O
#Blockchain O
#Dodgecoin O
#cryptocurrencynews O
Title O
: O
Major B-ORG_ORIG
Thai I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
Creates O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
Fund O
for O
Investments O
in O
Defi B-ORG_DEST
Description O
: O
Siam B-ORG_DEST
Commercial I-ORG_DEST
Bank I-ORG_DEST
, O
Thailand B-LOC_DEST
’ O
s O
oldest O
bank O
, O
is O
cementing O
its O
reputation O
as O
a O
strong O
funder O
of O
innovative O
financial O
technologies O
and O
Defi O
projects O
. O
This O
was O
made O
known O
in O
recent O
comments O
to O
fund O
blockchain O
startups O
. O
The O
institution O
’ O
s O
venture O
capital O
subsidiary O
, O
SCB O
10X O
, O
yesterday O
announced O
a O
new O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
fund O
dedicated O
to O
investments O
in O
global O
blockchain O
. O
This O
investment O
also O
extends O
[ O
… O
] O

#German O
#automotive O
@Continental B-ORG_ORIG
will O
start O
a O
development O
project O
in O
#Kaunas B-LOC_DEST
￼ O
It O
will O
double O
the O
production O
capacity O
and O
create O
additional O
500 O
new O
jobs O
. O
The O
total O
amount O
of O
investments O
will O
reach O
about O
185 B-MONEY
million I-MONEY
. I-MONEY
Eur I-MONEY
. I-MONEY
🏗 O
️ O
https://t.co/vX0GzZPcnW O
@invest_LT O
@KaunasFEZ O
Title O
: O
Automobilių O
elektronikos O
gamintoja O
„ O
Continental B-ORG_ORIG
“ O
Kaune O
sukurs O
500 O
naujų O
darbo O
vietų O
Description O
: O
Viena O
didžiausių O
investuotojų O
Lietuvoje O
, O
Vokietijos O
kapitalo O
automobilių O
elektronikos O
komponentų O
gamintoja O
„ O
Continental B-ORG_ORIG
“ O
į O
gamyklos O
Kauno O
laisvojoje O
ekonomikos O
zonoje O
( O
LEZ O
) O
plėtrą O
investuos O
dar O
daugiau O
nei O
90 O
mln O
. O
eurų O
. O
Įgyvendinus O
antrąjį O
plėtros O
etapą O
, O
„ O
Continental B-ORG_ORIG
“ O
investicijos O
Kaune O
sieks O
apie O
185 O
mln O
. O
eurų O
. O

Paratek B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
NUZYRA B-ORG_ORIG
® I-ORG_ORIG
Launch O
into O
the O
Community O
Setting O
https://t.co/Msqs1cqUqT O
#CABP O
#ABSSSI O
#antibiotics O
Title O
: O
Paratek B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
NUZYRA B-ORG_ORIG
® I-ORG_ORIG
Launch O
into O
the O
Community O
Setting O
Description O
: O
Paratek B-ORG_ORIG
Pharmaceuticals I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
Nasdaq B-ORG
: O
PRTK B-ORG_ORIG
) O
, O
a O
biopharmaceutical O
company O
that O
develops O
and O
commercializes O
life-saving O
therapies O
for O
public O
health O
threats O
in O

Dating O
juggernaut O
Match B-ORG_ORIG
buys O
Seoul B-LOC_DEST
- O
based O
Hyperconnect B-ORG_DEST
for O
$ B-MONEY
1.73 I-MONEY
B I-MONEY
, O
its O
biggest O
acquisition O
ever O
In O
a O
large O
win O
for O
the O
Korean O
startup O
ecosystem O
, O
dating O
powerhouse O
Match B-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
announced O
this O
afternoon O
that O
it O
would O
buy O
social O
networking O
company O
Hyperconne B-ORG_DEST
… O
https://t.co/u4VKHr5SjY O
https://t.co/FOGaq87Ibi O
Title O
: O
Dating O
juggernaut O
Match B-ORG_ORIG
buys O
Seoul B-LOC_DEST
- O
based O
Hyperconnect B-ORG_DEST
for O
$ B-MONEY
1.73 I-MONEY
B I-MONEY
, O
its O
biggest O
acquisition O
ever O
Description O
: O
This O
Blog O
is O
about O
all O
Latest O
Tech O
News O
in O
Worldwide O
from O
all O
Reputable O
and O
Authentic O
sources O
. O
Basic O
Aim O
Ownership O
Related O
Launched O
Articles O
& O
Videos O
. O

Huawei B-ORG_ORIG
has O
announced O
plans O
to O
create O
a O
further O
110 O
jobs O
in O
Ireland B-LOC_DEST
and O
will O
invest O
€ B-MONEY
80 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
Irish O
R O
& O
D O
. O
#jobs O
#irishjobs O
#techjobs O
@Huawei B-ORG_ORIG
https://t.co/G29eCwbOLO O
Title O
: O
Huawei B-ORG_ORIG
to O
create O
110 O
new O
Irish O
jobs O
Description O
: O
Huawei B-ORG_ORIG
has O
announced O
plans O
to O
create O
a O
further O
110 O
new O
jobs O
across O
Ireland B-LOC_DEST
by O
the O
end O
of O
2022 O
. O
The O
the O
newly O
created O
roles O
in O
sales O
, O
R O
& O
D O
and O
IT O
development O
will O
be O
based O
at O
the O
global O
ICT O
infrastructure O
firm's O
Dublin B-LOC_DEST
headquarters O
and O
a O
... O

ACQUISITION O
: O
@Doro_Care B-ORG_ORIG
, O
a O
telecare O
provider O
, O
has O
announced O
a O
new O
relationship O
with O
@TaDHousing B-ORG_DEST
, O
a O
provider O
of O
housing O
to O
clients O
in O
Staffordshire B-LOC_DEST
, O
North B-LOC_DEST
West I-LOC_DEST
Leicestershire I-LOC_DEST
and O
Derbyshire B-LOC_DEST
. O
Find O
out O
more O
: O
https://t.co/vwklm4Ts9X O
https://t.co/vZr20IMo4r O
Title O
: O
Telecare O
activity O
continues O
as O
Doro B-ORG_ORIG
acquires O
another O
TEC O
service O
• O
THIIS B-ORG
Magazine I-ORG
Description O
: O
Doro B-ORG_ORIG
has O
announced O
a O
new O
relationship O
with O
Trent B-ORG_DEST
and I-ORG_DEST
Dove I-ORG_DEST
Housing I-ORG_DEST
, O
a O
provider O
of O
housing O
to O
clients O
in O
Staffordshire B-LOC_DEST
, O
North B-LOC_DEST
West I-LOC_DEST
Leicestershire I-LOC_DEST
and O
Derbyshire B-LOC_DEST
. O

🦄 O
South B-LOC_DEST
Korea I-LOC_DEST
' O
s O
15th O
unicorn O
. O
Profitable O
, O
with O
$ B-MONEY
200M I-MONEY
revenue O
in O
2020 O
, O
+ O
50 O
% O
on O
2019 O
, O
Seoul B-LOC_DEST
- O
based O
social O
discovery O
& O
video O
company O
#Hyperconnect B-ORG_DEST
is O
being O
acquired O
by O
@Match B-ORG_ORIG
for O
$ B-MONEY
1.73 I-MONEY
B I-MONEY
, O
after O
early O
backing O
from O
@altosvc B-ORG
and O
@SoftBank B-ORG
Ventures I-ORG
Asia I-ORG
. O
https://t.co/QHTgEw9l5D O
https://t.co/R759t5wIdR O
Title O
: O
Hyperconnect B-ORG_DEST
company O
information O
, O
funding O
& O
investors O
Description O
: O
Hyperconnect B-ORG_DEST
, O
connecting O
people O
through O
shared O
interests O
and O
creating O
enjoyment O
. O
Here O
you'll O
find O
information O
about O
their O
funding O
, O
investors O
and O
team O
. O

October O
2020 O
: O
PKG B-ORG_ORIG
announced O
joint O
agreement O
with O
Adventus B-ORG_ORIG
Venture I-ORG_ORIG
to O
develop O
/ O
manufacture O
plans O
for O
two O
companies O
in O
their O
portfolio O
: O
Allevion B-ORG
Therapeutics I-ORG
and O
Pressao B-ORG
Medical I-ORG
. I-ORG
$ B-ORG
CBBT I-ORG
🔬 O

African O
#Tech O
impact O
fund O
secures O
capital O
from O
Ivory B-LOC_ORIG
Coast I-LOC_ORIG
, O
Luxembourg B-LOC_ORIG
governments O
. O
- O
The O
governments O
of O
Ivory B-LOC_ORIG
Coast I-LOC_ORIG
and O
Luxembourg B-LOC_ORIG
will O
invest O
a O
total O
of O
EUR B-MONEY
10 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
( O
US B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
12 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
) O
into O
Bamboo B-ORG_DEST
Capital I-ORG_DEST
... O
- O
#Funding O
#Growth O
#Investor O
#Startup O
- O
https://t.co/IoCSFOzJNS O
Title O
: O
African O
tech O
impact O
fund O
secures O
capital O
from O
Ivory B-LOC_ORIG
Coast I-LOC_ORIG
, O
Luxembourg B-LOC_ORIG
governments O
Description O
: O
The O
governments O
of O
Ivory B-LOC_ORIG
Coast I-LOC_ORIG
and O
Luxembourg B-LOC_ORIG
will O
invest O
a O
total O
of O
EUR B-MONEY
10 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
( O
US B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
12 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
) O
into O
Bamboo B-ORG_DEST
Capital I-ORG_DEST
Partner I-ORG_DEST
s O
’ O

Yelp B-ORG
Inc I-ORG
reported O
fourth-quarter O
earnings O
of O
$ B-MONEY
21.1 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
. O
On O
a O
per-share O
basis O
, O
the O
San O
Francisco-based O
company O
said O
it O
had O
net O
income O
of O
27 B-MONEY
cents I-MONEY
. O
The O
average O
estimate O
of O
seven O
analysts O
surveyed O
by O
Zacks B-ORG
Investment I-ORG
Research I-ORG
was O
for O
a O
loss O
of O
1 O
cent O
per O
share O
. O

@SearcherSeismic B-ORG_ORIG
has O
announced O
its O
expansion O
into O
the O
#mining O
sector O
with O
the O
completion O
of O
an O
airborne O
#exploration O
survey O
in O
Queensland B-LOC_DEST
, I-LOC_DEST
on O
behalf O
of O
@LongreachME B-ORG_ORIG
https://t.co/rw7LhVUH6e O

Armadale B-ORG
Capital I-ORG
PLC I-ORG
- O
Armadale B-ORG
Reports O
Successful O
Chinese O
EPC O
Test-Work O
#ACP B-ORG
@ArmadaleCapital B-ORG
https://t.co/Tfo1DeAQwV O
#voxmarkets O
#investing O
#shares O
#RNS O
via O
@voxmarkets O

We O
are O
pleased O
to O
announce O
the O
operation O
of O
our O
joint O
venture O
with O
@L3Harris B-ORG_ORIG
Tech O
one O
of O
North B-LOC
America I-LOC
’ O
s O
largest O
aerospace O
and O
defense O
manufacturers O
. O
#SAMIL3Harris O

. O
@tdcxgroup B-ORG_ORIG
the O
#technological O
company O
from O
Singapur B-LOC_ORIG
, O
opens O
its O
headquarters O
in O
#Barcelona B-LOC_DEST
with O
the O
support O
of O
@Catalonia_TI B-ORG
, O
the O
area O
of O
attraction O
of O
foreign O
investment O
of O
@accio_cat B-ORG
, O
the O
agency O
for O
the O
competitiveness O
of O
the O
@Generalitat_cat B-ORG
. O
https://t.co/63NgpUGwLk O
Title O
: O
La O
tecnológica O
TDCX B-ORG_ORIG
abre O
sede O
en O
Barcelona B-LOC_DEST
y O
creará O
hasta O
300 O
empleos O
Description O
: O
La O
empresa O
tecnológica O
de O
Singapur B-LOC_ORIG
Transformative B-ORG_ORIG
Digital I-ORG_ORIG
Customer I-ORG_ORIG
Experience I-ORG_ORIG
( O
TDCX B-ORG_ORIG
) O
ha O
abierto O
en O
Barcelona B-LOC_DEST
su O
primera O
oficina O
en O
Europa B-LOC_DEST
, O
en O
la O
que O
ha O
creado O
50 O
puestos O
de O
trabajo O
y O
espera O
duplicar O
su O
espacio O
de O
oficinas O
y O
llegar O
a O
los O
300 O
a O
finales O
de O
este O
año O

Big B-ORG
Rock I-ORG
Brewery I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
Announces O
Strategic O
Capital O
Plan O
in O
Calgary B-LOC
and O
Concurrent O
Credit O
Facility O
Expansion O
- O
Canada B-LOC
NewsWire B-ORG
https://t.co/B4ELF5KRhy O

Finch B-ORG_ORIG
Capital I-ORG_ORIG
Targets O
European O
Fintech O
Companies O
with O
€ B-MONEY
150 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
Fund O
The O
fund O
will O
invest O
in O
European O
technology O
companies O
with O
€ B-MONEY
2 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
to O
€ B-MONEY
5 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
revenues O
. O
https://t.co/W8YIPY4msD O
Title O
: O
Finch B-ORG_ORIG
Capital I-ORG_ORIG
Targets O
European O
Fintech O
Companies O
with O
€ B-MONEY
150 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
Fund I-MONEY
| O
Finance B-ORG
Magnates I-ORG
Description O
: O
Finch B-ORG_ORIG
Capital I-ORG_ORIG
announced O
the O
first O
close O
of O
Europe B-LOC_DEST
III O
, O
its O
€ B-MONEY
150 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
investment O
fund O
, O
to O
invest O
in O
the O
European O
fintech O
companies O
. O

Neo B-ORG_DEST
Lithium I-ORG_DEST
Corp I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
announces O
that O
Contemporary B-ORG_ORIG
Amperex I-ORG_ORIG
Technology I-ORG_ORIG
Co I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Limited I-ORG_ORIG
, O
a O
leading O
Chinese O
battery O
manufacturer O
and O
technology O
company O
. O
https://t.co/BLDWS5T7z9 O
1 O
of O
2 O
Title O
: O
CATL B-ORG_ORIG
increases O
investment O
in O
Neo B-ORG_DEST
Lithium I-ORG_DEST
- O
Canadian O
Manufacturing O
Description O
: O
CATL B-ORG_ORIG
to O
invest O
an O
additional O
C B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
2.6 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
and O
maintain O
its O
8 O
% O
equity O
ownership O
in O
Neo B-ORG_DEST
Lithium I-ORG_DEST
. O

@Pembroke_VCT B-ORG_ORIG
has O
invested O
£ B-MONEY
1 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
into O
@credentially_io B-ORG_DEST
, O
a O
platform O
that O
automates O
healthcare O
hiring O
, O
onboarding O
and O
compliance O
https://t.co/wV5yoFBdtt O
https://t.co/a6KvHUiajx O
Title O
: O
Pembroke B-ORG_ORIG
VCT I-ORG_ORIG
invests O
£ B-MONEY
1m I-MONEY
into O
healthcare O
software O
Credentially B-ORG_DEST
Description O
: O
Pembroke B-ORG_ORIG
VCT I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
venture O
capital O
trust O
focused O
on O
building O
the O
brands O
of O
tomorrow O
, O
has O
made O
an O
initial O
investment O
of O
£ B-MONEY
1 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
into O
Credentially B-ORG_DEST
, O
the O
platform O
that O
automates O
healthcare O
hiring O
, O
onboarding O
and O
compliance O
. O
During O
the O
pandemic O
, O
the O
company O
has O
worked O
with O
the O
NHS B-ORG
to O
speed O
up O
the O
registration O
of O
healthcare O
professionals O
. O

Tyson B-ORG_ORIG
Foods I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
$ B-ORG_ORIG
TSN I-ORG_ORIG
and O
Malayan B-ORG_DEST
Flour I-ORG_DEST
Mills I-ORG_DEST
Berhad I-ORG_DEST
$ B-ORG_DEST
MFLOUR I-ORG_DEST
today O
announced O
a O
partnership O
in O
which O
Tyson B-ORG_ORIG
Foods I-ORG_ORIG
will O
invest O
in O
the O
Malaysia B-LOC_DEST
- O
based O
company O
’ O
s O
vertically O
integrated O
poultry O
business O
, O
which O
will O
add O
more O
supply O
flexibility O
for O
both O
companies O
. O

ticker O
symbol O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
AUVI I-ORG_ORIG
Applied B-ORG_ORIG
UV I-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Acquisition O
of O
the O
Airocide B-ORG_DEST
( I-ORG_DEST
R I-ORG_DEST
) I-ORG_DEST
Technology O
Platform O
for O
Airborne O
Pathogen O
Reduction O
https://t.co/UuBJJJ5qCJ O
#premarket O
#stockmarket O
#news O
Title O
: O
Seeking B-ORG
Alpha I-ORG
| O
Stock O
Market O
Analysis O
& O
Tools O
for O
Investors O
Description O
: O
Join O
Seeking B-ORG
Alpha I-ORG
, O
the O
largest O
investing O
community O
in O
the O
world O
. O
Get O
stock O
market O
news O
and O
analysis O
, O
investing O
ideas O
, O
earnings O
calls O
, O
charts O
and O
portfolio O
analysis O
tools O
. O

#TmunityTherapeutics B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
#TCellEngineeredTherapy O
Collaboration O
https://t.co/Iy46AcPNV1 O

Blue B-ORG
Star I-ORG
Capital I-ORG
#BLU B-ORG
said O
its O
investee O
company O
Leaf B-ORG_ORIG
Mobile I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
, O
of O
which O
it O
holds O
10 O
% O
interest O
in O
, O
has O
completed O
its O
acquisition O
of O
East B-ORG_DEST
Side I-ORG_DEST
Games I-ORG_DEST
for O
approximately O
C B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
159 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
. O
@BlueStarCap B-ORG
https://t.co/PdJLr2X9jn O
#investing O
#shares O
#voxmarkets O
via O
@VOXmarkets O
Title O
: O
Blue B-ORG_ORIG
Star I-ORG_ORIG
’ I-ORG_ORIG
s I-ORG_ORIG
Leaf I-ORG_ORIG
Mobile I-ORG_ORIG
acquires O
East B-ORG_DEST
Side I-ORG_DEST
Games I-ORG_DEST
for O
$ B-MONEY
159m I-MONEY
- O
Vox B-ORG
Markets I-ORG
Description O
: O
Blue B-ORG
Star I-ORG
Capital I-ORG
, O
an O
investment O
group O
with O
a O
focus O
on O
new O
technologies O
such O
as O
esports O
, O
has O
announced O
that O
its O
investee O
company O
Leaf B-ORG_ORIG
Mobile I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
, O
of O
which O
it O
holds O
10 O
% O
interest O
in O
, O
has O
completed O
its O
acquisition O
of O
East B-ORG_DEST
Side I-ORG_DEST
Games I-ORG_DEST
for O
approximately O
C B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
159 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
. O

Absa B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
Kenya I-ORG_ORIG
is O
planning O
to O
invest O
over O
1.6 B-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
shillings I-MONEY
in O
technology O
to O
enhance O
service O
delivery O
as O
it O
marked O
one O
year O
since O
it O
rebranded O
from O
Barclays B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
Kenya I-ORG
https://t.co/Nm5zwhC6Qw O
#SokoNews O
Title O
: O
Absa B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
Kenya I-ORG_ORIG
To O
Invest O
Ksh B-MONEY
1.6 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
In O
Technology O
Description O
: O
Absa B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
Kenya I-ORG_ORIG
is O
planning O
to O
invest O
over O
1.6 B-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
shillings I-MONEY
in O
technology O
to O
enhance O
service O
delivery O

Acquisition O
in O
the O
ambient O
clinical O
intelligence O
space O
: O
Nuance B-ORG_ORIG
acquires O
Saykara B-ORG_DEST
to O
continue O
developing O
AI O
for O
streamlining O
clinical O
documentation O
@NuanceHealth B-ORG_ORIG
@SaykaraAI B-ORG_DEST
#patientexperience O
#doctorexperience O
#burnout O
#clinicalAI O
https://t.co/Tk359y62HW O
Title O
: O
Nuance B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Acquisition O
of O
Saykara B-ORG_DEST
Description O
: O
Nuance B-ORG_ORIG
Communications I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
NASDAQ B-ORG
: O
NUAN B-ORG_ORIG
) O
today O
announced O
the O
acquisition O
of O
Saykara B-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
Inc I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
, O
a O
like-minded O
startup O
focused O
on O
developing O
a O
mobile O
AI O
assistant O
to O
automate O
clinical O
documentation O
... O

CPR B-ORG_ORIG
Cell I-ORG_ORIG
Phone I-ORG_ORIG
Repair I-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
3 O
- O
Store O
Expansion O
https://t.co/AL6bAzFqHo O

Investment O
firm O
@SechaCapital B-ORG_ORIG
has O
been O
providing O
SMEs O
with O
capital O
and O
resources O
to O
help O
them O
expand O
by O
taking O
a O
minority O
stake O
in O
the O
company O
and O
provides O
capital O
of O
between O
R3 B-MONEY
million I-MONEY
and O
R15 B-MONEY
million I-MONEY
, O
but O
only O
invests O
for O
seven O
to O
ten O
years O
Check O
them O
@ O
https://t.co/DOxzBA0gxT O
Title O
: O
Secha B-ORG_ORIG
Capital I-ORG_ORIG
Partners I-ORG_ORIG
| O
Impact O
Investors O
in O
Africa B-LOC_DEST
Description O
: O
South O
African O
Impact O
Investing O
firm O
focusing O
the O
FMCG O
and O
Agribusiness O
Sectors O

Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
' O
s O
VC O
arm O
to O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
https://t.co/qQkIYipXcG O
Title O
: O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
' O
s O
VC O
arm O
to O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
Description O
: O
SCB B-ORG_ORIG
10X I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
venture O
capital O
unit O
of O
Thailand B-LOC_ORIG
' O
s O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
launched O
a O
new O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
fund O
to O
invest O
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
. O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
ALST I-ORG_ORIG
AllStar B-ORG_ORIG
Health I-ORG_ORIG
Brands I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
ALST B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
COVID O
- O
19 O
Testing O
Initiatives O
in O
South B-LOC_DEST
Africa I-LOC_DEST
and O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
ALST I-ORG_ORIG
https://t.co/OMAtQhnJIn O
Title O
: O
MOMO B-ORG
' O
S O
BREAKOUT O
BOARD O
Post O
# O
2185599 O
Description O
: O
MOMO B-ORG
' O
S O
BREAKOUT O
BOARD O
Message O
Board O
: O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
ALST I-ORG_ORIG
AllStar B-ORG_ORIG
Health I-ORG_ORIG
Brands I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
ALST B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Expansion O

@Philips B-ORG_ORIG
announced O
that O
it O
has O
completed O
the O
acquisition O
of O
@BioTelInc B-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
Inc I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
, O
an O
U B-LOC_DEST
. I-LOC_DEST
S I-LOC_DEST
. I-LOC_DEST
- O
based O
provider O
of O
remote O
#cardiac O
#diagnostics O
and O
#monitoring O
. O
https://t.co/pl5qAxDH8M O
Title O
: O
Philips B-ORG_ORIG
completes O
acquisition O
of O
BioTelemetry B-ORG_DEST
| O
industry O
news O
updates O
- O
India B-LOC
' O
s O
best O
industrial O
news O
video O
channel O
Description O
: O
Philips B-ORG_ORIG
completes O
acquisition O
of O
BioTelemetry B-ORG_DEST
Royal I-ORG_DEST
Philips B-ORG_ORIG
announced O
that O
it O
has O
completed O
the O
acquisition O
of O
BioTelemetry B-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
Inc I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
, O
an O
U B-LOC_DEST
. I-LOC_DEST
S I-LOC_DEST
. I-LOC_DEST
- O
based O
provider O
of O
remote O
cardiac O
diagnostics O
and O
monitoring O
. O
BioTelemetry B-ORG_DEST
’ O
s O
financial O
results O
will O
be O
consolidated O
as O
part O
of O
Philips B-ORG_ORIG
’ O
Connected B-ORG_ORIG
Care I-ORG_ORIG
business O
segment O
as O
of O
February O
9 O
. O
The O
acquisition O
of O
BioTelemetry B-ORG_DEST
is O
a O
… O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
ALST I-ORG_ORIG
AllStar B-ORG_ORIG
Health I-ORG_ORIG
Brands I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
ALST B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
COVID O
- O
19 O
Testing O
Initiatives O
in O
South B-LOC_DEST
Africa I-LOC_DEST
an O
https://t.co/wZYc8rSkxm O
Title O
: O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
ALST I-ORG_ORIG
AllStar B-ORG_ORIG
Health I-ORG_ORIG
Brands I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
- O
SmallCapGoodies O
#6048355 O
- O
Investors O
Hangout O
Description O
: O
SmallCapGoodies O
: O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
ALST I-ORG_ORIG
AllStar B-ORG_ORIG
Health I-ORG_ORIG
Brands I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
ALST B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
COVID O
- O
19 O
Testing O
Initiatives O
in O
South B-LOC_DEST
- O
#6048355 O

Acquisition O
/ O
Contract O
Specialist O
, O
Mid O
: O
Booz B-ORG
Allen I-ORG
Hamilton I-ORG
, O
USA B-LOC
( O
California B-LOC
) O
. O
https://t.co/AUpFZ3V5zN O
#MBA O
#jobs O
#USA B-LOC
Title O
: O
MBA-Exchange.com O
- O
Job O
Detail O
Description O
: O

SCB B-ORG_ORIG
10X I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
venture O
arm O
of O
Thailand B-LOC_ORIG
’ O
s O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
announced O
it O
will O
create O
a O
new O
USD B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
VC O
fund O
dedicated O
to O
investing O
in O
global O
early O
and O
growth O
stage O
blockchain O
, O
decentralized O
finance O
( O
DeFi O
) O
, O
and O
digital O
asset O
startups O
. O
https://t.co/MjonoLxAhN O
Title O
: O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
venture O
arm O
creates O
new O
$ B-MONEY
50M I-MONEY
blockchain O
fund O
» O
CryptoNinjas B-ORG
Description O
: O
SCB B-ORG_ORIG
10X I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
venture O
arm O
of O
Thailand B-LOC_ORIG
' O
s O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
announced O
it O
will O
create O
a O
new O
USD B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
VC O
fund O
dedicated O
to O
investing O
in O
global O

Solarise B-ORG_ORIG
Africa I-ORG_ORIG
, O
a O
Pan-African O
energy O
leasing O
company O
, O
has O
announced O
its O
expansion O
into O
three O
new O
countries O
in O
Africa B-LOC_DEST
after O
signing O
a O
partnership O
agreement O
with O
Centennial B-ORG_DEST
Generating I-ORG_DEST
Co I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
#SOLAR O
https://t.co/6xkb0BksuH O
Title O
: O
Solarise B-ORG_ORIG
Africa I-ORG_ORIG
Expands O
Energy O
Footprint O
in O
Africa B-LOC_DEST
Description O
: O
Solarise B-ORG_ORIG
Africa I-ORG_ORIG
, O
a O
Pan-African O
energy O
leasing O
company O
, O
has O
announced O
its O
expansion O
into O
three O
new O
countries O
in O
Africa B-LOC_DEST
after O
signing O
a O
partnership O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
NEPT I-ORG_ORIG
( O
2.61 O
) O
up O
3 O
announced O
the O
acquisition O
of O
a O
controlling O
interest O
in O
Sprout B-ORG_DEST
Foods I-ORG_DEST
( O
" O
Sprout B-ORG_DEST
" O
) O
, O
a O
portfolio O
investment O
of O
Morgan B-ORG_DEST
Stanley I-ORG_DEST
Expansion I-ORG_DEST
Capital I-ORG_DEST
( O
" O
MSEC B-ORG_DEST
" O
) O
. O

$ B-ORG
CNNE I-ORG
Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
Announces O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
I I-ORG
Filing O
of O
S O
- O
1 O
https://t.co/T1m0uHmnXo O
Title O
: O
Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
Announces O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
I I-ORG
| O
CNNE B-ORG
Stock O
News O
Description O
: O
Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
( O
NYSE B-ORG
: O
CNNE B-ORG
) O
( O
“ O
Cannae B-ORG
” O
or O
the O
“ O
Company O
” O
) O
today O
announced O
that O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
I I-ORG

Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
I I-ORG
announces O
filing O
of O
S O
- O
1 O
$ B-ORG
CNNE I-ORG

Government B-ORG_ORIG
announces O
to O
invest O
Rs B-MONEY
. I-MONEY
400 I-MONEY
crores I-MONEY
in O
Goa B-LOC_DEST
to O
make O
it O
fisheries O
hub O
#currentaffairs O
https://t.co/3pvVyW0k05 O
Title O
: O
Government B-ORG_ORIG
announces O
to O
invest O
Rs B-MONEY
. I-MONEY
400 I-MONEY
crores I-MONEY
in O
Goa B-LOC_DEST
to O
make O
it O
fisheries O
hub O
Description O
: O
The O
Union O
Government B-ORG_ORIG
has O
already O
sanctioned O
Rs B-MONEY
. I-MONEY
41.7 I-MONEY
crores I-MONEY
to O
the O
state O
, O
which O
will O
help O
in O
reviving O
the O
fisheries O
industry O
and O
ensure O
safe O
fishing O
. O

Ocado B-ORG_ORIG
has O
announced O
that O
it O
plans O
to O
invest O
£ B-MONEY
700m I-MONEY
into O
new O
projects O
for O
its O
technology O
clients O
in O
2021 O
. O
https://t.co/JxHlgJ0thH O
Title O
: O
Grocery O
shopping O
has O
changed O
for O
good O
, O
says O
Ocado B-ORG_ORIG
Description O
: O
The O
online O
supermarket O
says O
the O
Covid O
pandemic O
has O
permanently O
changed O
the O
grocery O
landscape O
worldwide O
. O

Thailand B-LOC_ORIG
' O
s O
oldest O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
launched O
a O
new O
$ B-MONEY
50m I-MONEY
fund O
to O
invest O
in O
blockchain O
& O
DeFi O
https://t.co/WLLqXZazih O
Title O
: O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
' O
s O
VC O
arm O
to O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
Description O
: O
SCB B-ORG_ORIG
10X I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
venture O
capital O
unit O
of O
Thailand B-LOC_ORIG
' O
s O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
launched O
a O
new O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
fund O
to O
invest O
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
. O

Bollington B-ORG_ORIG
Strengthens O
Corporate O
Offering O
with O
Watson B-ORG_DEST
Laurie I-ORG_DEST
Ltd I-ORG_DEST
Acquisition O
. O
Bollington B-ORG_ORIG
has O
today O
announced O
that O
it O
has O
completed O
the O
purchase O
of O
North B-LOC_DEST
West I-LOC_DEST
based O
corporate O
insurance O
broker O
, O
Watson B-ORG_DEST
Laurie I-ORG_DEST
Ltd I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
https://t.co/DzfO4yFNyt O

Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
KHRN I-ORG_ORIG
https://t.co/nTMwr6rHqx O
Title O
: O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
Description O
: O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
to O
launch O
two O
additional O
small-format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
clinics O
in O
major O
metropolitan O
centres O
outside O
of O
Bogota B-LOC_DEST
in O
early O
March O
2021 O
, O
following O
successful O
launch O
... O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
AWK I-ORG_ORIG
California B-ORG_ORIG
American I-ORG_ORIG
Water I-ORG_ORIG
Invested O
More O
Than O
$ B-MONEY
68 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
in O
Infrastructure O
Improvements O
In O
2020 O
https://t.co/iJlYI4Lg9R O
Title O
: O
California B-ORG_ORIG
American I-ORG_ORIG
Water I-ORG_ORIG
Invested O
More O
Than O
$ B-MONEY
68 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
in O
| O
AWK B-ORG_ORIG
Stock O
News O
Description O
: O
California B-ORG_ORIG
American I-ORG_ORIG
Water I-ORG_ORIG
recently O
announced O
its O
end-of-year O
investment O
total O
and O
system O
improvements O
for O
2020 O
. O
More O
than O
$ B-MONEY
68 I-MONEY

Hyzon B-ORG_ORIG
Motors I-ORG_ORIG
, O
a O
global O
supplier O
of O
zero-emissions O
hydrogen O
fuel O
cell O
powered O
commercial O
vehicles O
, O
and O
Decarbonization B-ORG_ORIG
Plus I-ORG_ORIG
Acquisition I-ORG_ORIG
Corp I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
, O
announced O
a O
definitive O
agreement O
for O
a O
business O
combination O
that O
would O
result O
in O
#Hyzon B-ORG_DEST
becoming O
a O
publicly O
listed O
company O
on O
the O
NASDAQ B-ORG

$ B-ORG
CNNE I-ORG
Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
Announces O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
II I-ORG
Filing O
of O
S O
- O
1 O
https://t.co/YbWZRUKRbz O
Title O
: O
Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
Announces O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
II I-ORG
| O
CNNE B-ORG
Stock O
News O
Description O
: O
Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
( O
NYSE B-ORG
: O
CNNE B-ORG
) O
( O
“ O
Cannae B-ORG
” O
or O
the O
“ O
Company O
” O
) O
today O
announced O
that O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
II I-ORG

California B-ORG_ORIG
American I-ORG_ORIG
Water I-ORG_ORIG
Invested O
More O
Than O
$ B-MONEY
68 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
in O
Infrastructure O
Improvements O
In O
2020 O
https://t.co/iDw0xyIv4q O
Title O
: O
California B-ORG_ORIG
American I-ORG_ORIG
Water I-ORG_ORIG
Invested O
More O
Than O
$ B-MONEY
68 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
in O
Infrastructure O
Improvements O
In O
2020 O
Description O
: O
California B-ORG_ORIG
American I-ORG_ORIG
Water I-ORG_ORIG
recently O
announced O
its O
end-of-year O
investment O
total O
and O
system O
improvements O
for O
2020 O
. O
More O
than O
$ B-MONEY
68 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
total O
was O
invest O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
KHRN I-ORG_ORIG
$ B-ORG_ORIG
KHRNF I-ORG_ORIG
@KhironLife B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
🇨 B-LOC_DEST
🇴 I-LOC_DEST
#Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
#PotStocks O
#cannabisnewsDD O
https://t.co/QHIdkkHTVi O
Title O
: O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
Description O
: O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
to O
launch O
two O
additional O
small-format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
clinics O
in O
major O
metropolitan O
centres O
outside O
of O
Bogota B-LOC_DEST
in O
early O
March O
2021 O
, O
following O
successful O
launch O
... O

OnePlus B-ORG_ORIG
announces O
expansion O
of O
OnePlus B-ORG_ORIG
smart O
TV O
portfolio O
Bangalore B-LOC
, O
8 O
June O
2020 O
: O
OnePlus B-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
global O
premium O
technology O
brand O
, O
today O
announced O
that O
it O
will O
expand O
its O
https://t.co/ilWJtD1PlL O
Title O
: O
OnePlus B-ORG_ORIG
announces O
expansion O
of O
OnePlus B-ORG_ORIG
smart O
TV O
portfolio O
- O
SwadeshiRating.in O
Description O
: O
The O
Posts O
of O
swadeshirating.in O
contains O
carefully O
chosen O
and O
detailed O
content O
about O
the O
Indian O
companies O
and O
their O
products O
, O
we O
give O
researched O
and O
detailed O
articles O
on O
each O
topic O
. O

AllStar B-ORG_ORIG
Health I-ORG_ORIG
Brands I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
ALST B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
COVID O
- O
19 O
Testing O
Initiatives O
in O
South B-LOC_DEST
Africa I-LOC_DEST
and O
Other O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
ALST I-ORG_ORIG
https://t.co/teotvGrHUN O
Title O
: O
Allstar B-ORG_ORIG
Health I-ORG_ORIG
Brands I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
ALST B-ORG_ORIG
Post O
# O
20625 O
Description O
: O
Allstar B-ORG_ORIG
Health I-ORG_ORIG
Brands I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
ALST B-ORG_ORIG
Stock O
Message O
Board O
: O
AllStar B-ORG_ORIG
Health I-ORG_ORIG
Brands I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
ALST B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Expansion O
of O

SCB B-ORG_ORIG
10X I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
venture O
capital O
unit O
of O
Thailand B-LOC_ORIG
' O
s O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
launched O
a O
new O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
fund O
to O
invest O
in O
blockchain O
and O
decentralized O
finance O
... O
Read O
more O
: O
https://t.co/EttAf7RMkR O
Title O
: O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
' O
s O
VC O
arm O
to O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
Description O
: O
SCB B-ORG_ORIG
10X I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
venture O
capital O
unit O
of O
Thailand B-LOC_ORIG
' O
s O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
launched O
a O
new O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
fund O
to O
invest O
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
. O

Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
https://t.co/DvW2b1P5xx O
Title O
: O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ O
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
Description O
: O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O

$ B-ORG
CNNE I-ORG
[ O
15s O
. O
delayed O
]: O
Issued O
Press O
Release O
on O
February O
10 O
, O
06:32 O
: O
00 O
: O
Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
Announces O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
II I-ORG
Filing O
of O
S O
- O
1 O
https://t.co/u3Vwx2aHsQ O
Title O
: O
Flash O
Alert O
Description O
: O
Real-time O
alerts O
about O
equities O
, O
ETFs O
, O
cryptocurrencies O
and O
more O
sent O
to O
any O
device O

Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
Announces O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
II I-ORG
Filing O
of O
S O
- O
1 O
https://t.co/Pvx7dGwSvt O
Title O
: O
Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
Announces O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
II I-ORG
Filing O
of O
S O
- O
1 O
Description O
: O
Feb O
. O
10 O
, O
2021 O
11:32 O
UTC O
Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
Announces O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
II I-ORG
Filing O
of O
S O
- O
1 O

$ B-ORG
CNNE I-ORG
[ O
15s O
. O
delayed O
]: O
Issued O
Press O
Release O
on O
February O
10 O
, O
06:29 O
: O
00 O
: O
Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG
Announces O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
I I-ORG
Filing O
of O
S O
- O
1 O
https://t.co/UPih7gmjrh O
Title O
: O
Flash O
Alert O
Description O
: O
Real-time O
alerts O
about O
equities O
, O
ETFs O
, O
cryptocurrencies O
and O
more O
sent O
to O
any O
device O

Cannae B-ORG
Holdings I-ORG
announces O
Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corp I-ORG
. I-ORG
II I-ORG
filing O
of O
S O
- O
1 O
$ O
CNNE O

The O
venture O
capital O
unit O
of O
Thailand B-LOC_ORIG
' O
s O
oldest O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
launched O
a O
new O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
fund O
to O
invest O
in O
blockchain O
and O
decentralized O
finance O
( O
DeFi O
) O
startups O
https://t.co/DNTvg0lXbJ O
Title O
: O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
' O
s O
VC O
arm O
to O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
Description O
: O
SCB B-ORG_ORIG
10X I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
venture O
capital O
unit O
of O
Thailand B-LOC_ORIG
' O
s O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
launched O
a O
new O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
fund O
to O
invest O
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
. O

A O
conglomerate O
in O
Energy O
, O
Hospitality O
and O
Real O
Estate O
sectors O
across O
three O
continents O
, O
Janus B-ORG_ORIG
Continental I-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
( O
JCG B-ORG_ORIG
) O
, O
has O
invested O
$ B-MONEY
13 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
Highview B-ORG_DEST
Enterprises I-ORG_DEST
. O
#Africa B-LOC
First O
#Africa B-LOC
News O
#NewsCentralTV O
https://t.co/mqNZWNzbYn O
Title O
: O
Janus B-ORG_ORIG
Continental I-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
Invests O
$ B-MONEY
13m I-MONEY
in O
Highview B-ORG_DEST
Enterprises I-ORG_DEST
Power I-ORG_DEST
Description O
: O
The O
investment O
will O
tackle O
the O
renewable O
energy O
storage O
gap O
that O
currently O
exists O
across O
the O
continent O
, O
where O
nearly O
600m O
people O
live O
without O
access O
to O
electricity O
. O

The O
European B-ORG_ORIG
Investment I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
( O
EIB B-ORG_ORIG
) O
approved O
a O
EUR B-MONEY
600 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
package O
for O
Valeo B-ORG_DEST
to O
finance O
its O
research O
projects O
focused O
on O
reducing O
CO2 O
emissions O
and O
improving O
vehicle O
safety O
. O
#Valeo B-ORG_DEST
#EIB B-ORG_ORIG

Previously O
in O
our O
blog O
: O
Garmin B-ORG_ORIG
Announced O
It O
’ O
s O
Completes O
Acquisition O
Of O
Navigon B-ORG_DEST
https://t.co/Wz3aHo2XEY O
Title O
: O
Garmin B-ORG_ORIG
Announced O
It's O
Completes O
Acquisition O
Of O
Navigon B-ORG_DEST
- O
The O
Tech O
Journal O
Description O
: O
Garmin B-ORG_ORIG
has O
delivered O
85 O
million O
GPS O
enabled O
devices O
far O
more O
than O
any O
other O
navigation O
provider O
Since O
its O
inception O
in O
1989 O
. O
Garmin B-ORG_ORIG
Ltd I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
global O
leader O
in O
satellite O
navigation O
, O
announced O
it O
has O
completed O
the O
acquisition O
of O
Navigon B-ORG_DEST
AG I-ORG_DEST
, O
a O
privately-held O
navigation O
provider O
headquartered O
in O
Hamburg B-LOC_DEST
, O
Germany B-LOC_DEST
. O

[ O
RECAP O
] O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
TSN I-ORG_ORIG
Tyson B-ORG_ORIG
Foods I-ORG_ORIG
, O
Malayan B-ORG_DEST
Flour I-ORG_DEST
Mills I-ORG_DEST
Berhad I-ORG_DEST
announce O
partnership O
Tyson B-ORG_ORIG
Foods I-ORG_ORIG
and O
Malayan B-ORG_DEST
Flour I-ORG_DEST
Mills I-ORG_DEST
Berhad I-ORG_DEST
announced O
a O
partnership O
in O
which O
Tyson B-ORG_ORIG
Foods I-ORG_ORIG
will O
invest O
in O
the O
Malaysia B-LOC_DEST
- O
based O
company's O
vertically O
integrated O
... O
https://t.co/8WEF1Apb6G O
Title O
: O
Soumyajyoti O
Biswas O
( O
@sbiswas O
) O
| O
Stocktwits O
Description O
: O
[ O
RECAP O
] O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
TSN I-ORG_ORIG
Tyson B-ORG_ORIG
Foods I-ORG_ORIG
, O
Malayan B-ORG_DEST
Flour I-ORG_DEST
Mills I-ORG_DEST
Berhad I-ORG_DEST
announce O
partnership O
Tyson B-ORG_ORIG
Foods I-ORG_ORIG
and O
Malayan B-ORG_DEST
Flour I-ORG_DEST
Mills I-ORG_DEST
Berhad I-ORG_DEST
announced O
a O
partnership O
in O
which O
Tyson B-ORG_ORIG
Foods I-ORG_ORIG
will O
invest O
in O
the O
Malaysia B-LOC_DEST
- O
based O
company's O
vertically O
integrated O
poultry O
business O
, O
which O
will O
add O
more O
supply O
flexibility O
for O
both O
companies O
. O
The O
transaction O
is O
subject O
to O
approval O
by O
the O
shareholders O
of O
Malayan B-ORG_DEST
Flour I-ORG_DEST
Mills I-ORG_DEST
Berhad I-ORG_DEST
, O
amongst O
others O
. O
Read O
more O
at O
: O
https://thefly.com/n.php?id=3244485 O
View O
the O
full O
list O
of O
news O
/ O
momentum O
plays O
on O
watch O
at O
: O
bit.ly/32GfaRt O
[ O
No O
bias O
/ O
position O
] O
[ O
Find O
me O
at O
https://stocktwits.com/sbiswas O
| O
https://twitter.com/soumyajyoti_b O
] O
" O

Wells B-ORG_ORIG
Fargo I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
in O
6 O
Black-Owned O
Banks O
https://t.co/Yse1EWUls7 O
Title O
: O
Wells B-ORG_ORIG
Fargo I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
in O
6 O
Black-Owned O
Banks O
Description O
: O
Wells B-ORG_ORIG
Fargo I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
multinational O
financial O
services O
company O
, O
has O
announced O
investments O
in O
six O
Black O
Minority O
Depository O
Institutions O
( O
MSIs O
) O
. O

Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
' O
s O
VC O
arm O
to O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
#Startup O
#blockchain O
via O
https://t.co/cBj7YRwrst O
https://t.co/CuuIxkJtsu O
Title O
: O
Twinybots O
– O
Empower O
your O
business O
Description O
: O
Title O
: O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
' O
s O
VC O
arm O
to O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
Description O
: O
SCB B-ORG_ORIG
10X I-ORG_ORIG
, O
the O
venture O
capital O
unit O
of O
Thailand B-LOC_ORIG
' O
s O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Commercial I-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
launched O
a O
new O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
fund O
to O
invest O
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
. O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
TYL I-ORG_ORIG
$ B-ORG_DEST
EGOV I-ORG_DEST
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
https://t.co/EmMW5Q7TR4 O
Title O
: O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
| O
TYL O
Stock O
News O
Description O
: O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
NYSE B-ORG
: O
TYL B-ORG_ORIG
) O
and O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
Inc I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
( O
NASDAQ B-ORG
: O
EGOV B-ORG_DEST
) O
, O
jointly O
announced O
today O
that O
they O
have O
entered O
into O
a O

@AbsaKenya B-ORG_ORIG
@AbsaKenya B-ORG_ORIG
is O
planning O
to O
invest O
over O
1.6 B-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
shillings I-MONEY
in O
technology O
to O
enhance O
service O
delivery O
as O
it O
marked O
one O
year O
since O
it O
rebranded O
from O
Barclays B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of O
Kenya B-LOC_ORIG
https://t.co/aI2DT9ckuG O
#SokoNews O
#WeAreOneWithYou O
Title O
: O
Absa B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
Kenya I-ORG_ORIG
To O
Invest O
Ksh B-MONEY
1.6 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
In O
Technology O
Description O
: O
Absa B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
Kenya I-ORG_ORIG
is O
planning O
to O
invest O
over O
1.6 B-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
shillings O
in O
technology O
to O
enhance O
service O
delivery O

$ B-ORG
KHRNF I-ORG
[ I-ORG
15s O
. O
delayed O
]: O
Issued O
Press O
Release O
on B-ORG
February I-ORG
10 I-ORG
, I-ORG
0 I-ORG
6:30 O
: O
00 O
: O
Khiron O
Announces O
Ex O
pansion B-ORG
of I-ORG
Small-Format I-ORG
Zeren I-ORG
ia O
™ O
Clin O
ics B-ORG
in I-ORG
C I-ORG
olombia O
Follo O
wing B-ORG
Suc I-ORG
cess O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
https://t.co/ O
0U0WlutI6y B-ORG
Title I-ORG
: I-ORG
F I-ORG
lash O
Alert O
Description O
: O
Real-time O
alerts O
about O
equities O
, O
ETFs O
, O
cryptocurrencies O
and O
more O
sent O
to O
any O
device O

Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
https://t.co/lm2Z4waMEv O
Title O
: O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
Description O
: O
Feb O
. O
10 O
, O
2021 O
11:45 O
UTC O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
TYL I-ORG_ORIG
[ O
15s O
. O
delayed O
]: O
Issued O
Press O
Release O
on O
February O
10 O
, O
06:45 O
: O
00 O
: O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
https://t.co/2UFAirtGA1 O
Title O
: O
Flash O
Alert O
Description O
: O
Real-time O
alerts O
about O
equities O
, O
ETFs O
, O
cryptocurrencies O
and O
more O
sent O
to O
any O
device O

Today O
, O
I'm O
thrilled O
to O
announce O
that O
Iconscout B-ORG_DEST
has O
been O
acquired O
by O
@LottieFiles B-ORG_ORIG
https://t.co/Y7wT38GCDW O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
KHRNF I-ORG_ORIG
#OTCQX B-ORG
International I-ORG
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Life I-ORG_ORIG
Sciences I-ORG_ORIG
Corp I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
KHRNF B-ORG_ORIG
: O
OTCQX B-ORG
International I-ORG
) O
| O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
https://t.co/XzwYCOoIdS O
Title O
: O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
KHRNF I-ORG_ORIG
#OTCQX B-ORG
International I-ORG
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Life I-ORG_ORIG
Sciences I-ORG_ORIG
Corp I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
KHRNF B-ORG_ORIG
: O
... O
Description O
: O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
KHRNF I-ORG_ORIG
#OTCQX B-ORG
International I-ORG
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Life I-ORG_ORIG
Sciences I-ORG_ORIG
Corp I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
KHRNF B-ORG_ORIG
: O
OTCQX B-ORG
International I-ORG
) O
| O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
... O

$ B-ORG_DEST
EGOV I-ORG_DEST
NEW O
ARTICLE O
: O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
https://t.co/jpNn3mH6kY O
Get O
all O
the O
latest O
$ B-ORG_DEST
EGOV I-ORG_DEST
related O
news O
here O
: O
https://t.co/745nF2YijG O
https://t.co/4pblPzcJZh O
Title O
: O
EGOV B-ORG_DEST
: O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
- O
STCK.PRO O
Description O
: O
PLANO B-LOC
, O
Texas B-LOC
& O
OLATHE B-LOC
, O
Kan B-LOC
. I-LOC
- O
- O
( O
BUSINESS B-ORG
WIRE I-ORG
) O
- O
- O
- O
$ B-ORG_DEST
EGOV I-ORG_DEST
#tylertech B-ORG_ORIG
- O
- O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
a O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
all-cash O
transaction O
. O
Title O
: O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
( O
EGOV B-ORG_DEST
) O
Latest O
Stock O
News O
- O
STCK.PRO O
Description O
: O
Latest O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
( O
EGOV B-ORG_DEST
) O
stock O
news O
, O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
Inc I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
is O
a O
digital O
government O
services O
, O
which O
through O
its O
subsidiaries O
, O
engages O
in O
the O
provision O
... O

After O
Asos B-ORG_ORIG
acquired O
#Topshop B-ORG_DEST
and O
other O
labels O
, O
#BooHoo B-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
Plc I-ORG_ORIG
acquired O
the O
remaining O
brands O
from O
Philip O
Green O
’ O
s O
failed O
Arcadia B-ORG
#Group I-ORG
. O
As O
per O
#business O
of O
#fashion O
, O
Boohoo B-ORG_ORIG
has O
agreed O
to O
buy O
the O
Dorothy B-ORG_DEST
Perkins I-ORG_DEST
, O
Burton B-ORG_DEST
and O
Wallis B-ORG_DEST
... O
https://t.co/o1YaKUxnM3 O
Title O
: O
Boohoo B-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
acquires O
Arcadia B-ORG
brands O
for O
$ B-MONEY
34 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
Description O
: O
Boohoo B-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
acquires O
Arcadia B-ORG
brands O
for O
$ B-MONEY
34 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY

#SFHolding B-ORG_ORIG
to O
take O
over O
@KerryLogistics B-ORG_DEST
for O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
. O
The O
#Chinese O
courier O
plans O
to O
buy O
a O
51.8 O
per O
cent O
stake O
in O
#HongKong B-LOC_DEST
- O
listed O
Kerry B-ORG_DEST
Logistics I-ORG_DEST
at O
HK B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
18.8 I-MONEY
per O
share O
. O
#logistics O
#supplychain O
#investment O
#kerrygroup B-ORG_DEST
#logisticscompany B-ORG_ORIG
https://t.co/9bTOq9ssgH O
Title O
: O
SF B-ORG_ORIG
Holding I-ORG_ORIG
to O
take O
over O
Kerry B-ORG_DEST
Logistics I-ORG_DEST
for O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
Description O
: O
The O
Chinese O
courier O
plans O
to O
buy O
a O
51.8 O
per O
cent O
stake O
in O
Hong B-LOC_DEST
Kong I-LOC_DEST
- O
listed O
Kerry B-ORG_DEST
Logistics I-ORG_DEST
at O
HK B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
18.8 I-MONEY
per O
share O
, O
according O
to O
a O
joint O
statement O
to O
the O
Hong B-LOC_DEST
Kong I-LOC_DEST
stock O
exchange O
on O
Wednesday O
. O

Austerlitz B-ORG
Acquisition I-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
I I-ORG
Announces O
Filing O
of O
S O
- O
1 O
https://t.co/zLHxDKd7WA O
#StockMarket O
#Stocks O

The O
$ B-MONEY
53.7 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
investment O
is O
expected O
to O
add O
30 O
new O
jobs O
over O
the O
next O
five O
years O
. O
https://t.co/R7VIxv8tYY O
Title O
: O
Lonza B-ORG_ORIG
announces O
$ B-MONEY
53.7 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
investment O
to O
expand O
Greenwood B-LOC_DEST
County I-LOC_DEST
operations O
- O
UPSTATE B-ORG
BUSINESS I-ORG
JOURNAL I-ORG
Description O
: O
Pharmaceutical O
, O
biotech O
and O
nutrition O
supplier O
Lonza B-ORG_ORIG
announced O
plans O
Feb O
. O
2 O
to O
expand O
its O
Greenwood B-LOC_DEST
County I-LOC_DEST
operations O
at O
535 O
N O
. O
Emerald O
Road O
in O
Greenwood B-LOC_DEST
. O
The O
$ B-MONEY
53.7 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
investment O
is O
expected O
to O
add O
30 O
new O
jobs O
over O
the O
next O
five O
years O
. O

Brewing O
giant O
#Kirin B-ORG
announced O
that O
it O
will O
end O
its O
joint O
venture O
with O
a O
company O
in O
#Burma B-LOC
that O
was O
found O
to O
be O
linked O
to O
the O
country's O
military O
. O
https://t.co/XKnqDYCIIH O
https://t.co/DiD3kyApOr O
Title O
: O
Japan B-LOC
' O
s O
Kirin B-ORG
ditches O
Myanmar B-LOC
beer O
partner O
because O
of O
its O
ties O
to O
the O
military O
Description O
: O
Japanese O
companies O
bet O
on O
Myanmar B-LOC
years O
ago O
as O
the O
Southeast O
Asian O
country O
emerged O
from O
decades O
of O
military O
rule O
. O
But O
this O
week's O
coup O
has O
already O
ended O
one O
of O
those O
deals O
. O

Max B-ORG_ORIG
Crowdfund I-ORG_ORIG
announces O
a O
strategic O
partnership O
within O
New B-LOC_DEST
Zealand I-LOC_DEST
. O
The O
fintech O
platform O
built O
on O
blockchain O
technology O
is O
launching O
in O
New B-LOC_DEST
Zealand I-LOC_DEST
under O
the O
name O
Max B-ORG_DEST
Crowdfund I-ORG_DEST
NZ I-ORG_DEST
Agency I-ORG_DEST
Limited I-ORG_DEST
. O
Link O
to O
all O
the O
info O
: O
https://t.co/czBtMtRwcV O
#investing O
#DailyFinance O
#crowdfund O
https://t.co/ITT39TRlbP O
Title O
: O
Real O
Estate O
Crowdfunding O
Hits O
New B-LOC_DEST
Zealand I-LOC_DEST
- O
Max B-ORG_ORIG
Property I-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
Description O
: O
Max B-ORG_ORIG
Property I-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
announces O
a O
strategic O
partnership O
within O
New B-LOC_DEST
Zealand I-LOC_DEST
to O
launch O
a O
crowdfunding O
platform O
. O
Read O
more O
about O
it O
! O

Thanks O
, O
@mgretailer O
for O
the O
piece O
on O
our O
Indoor O
AgTech O
startups O
. O
#agtech O
#indooragtech O
#indoorfarming O
#indoorgrowing O
#innovation O
#technology O
#tech O
#sente O
#sentefoundry O
https://t.co/bGcASdSmIA O
Title O
: O
Sente B-ORG_ORIG
Foundry I-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Investment O
in O
Five O
Indoor O
AgTech O
Startups O
Description O
: O
CHICAGO B-LOC
– O
Sente B-ORG_ORIG
Foundry I-ORG_ORIG
LLC I-ORG_ORIG
( O
" O
Sente B-ORG_ORIG
" O
) O
, O
in O
partnership O
with O
GrowRay B-ORG_ORIG
Lighting I-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
and O
NOBO B-ORG_ORIG
, O
announces O
five O
startups O
selected O
for O
investment O
and O
three O
named O
ecosystem O
partners O
through O
its O
collaborative O
due-diligence O
and O
mentoring O
program O
, O
Indoor O
AgTech O
. O
Pro O

ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O
https://t.co/yGQrz08IP6 O
Title O
: O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O
Description O
: O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O

VC O
firm O
Finch B-ORG_ORIG
Capital I-ORG_ORIG
has O
announced O
the O
successful O
closure O
of O
its O
€ B-MONEY
150m I-MONEY
‘ O
Europe B-ORG_ORIG
III I-ORG_ORIG
’ O
fund O
for O
investing O
in O
Series O
A O
and O
B O
fintech O
startups O
https://t.co/kZclS7LgbJ O
#Funding O
#Startups O
#VentureCapital O
#Fintech O
Title O
: O
Finch B-ORG_ORIG
Capital I-ORG_ORIG
closes O
€ B-MONEY
150m I-MONEY
fund O
for O
European O
fintech O
Description O
: O
VC O
firm O
Finch B-ORG_ORIG
Capital I-ORG_ORIG
has O
announced O
the O
successful O
closure O
of O
its O
€ B-MONEY
150m I-MONEY
‘ O
Europe B-ORG_ORIG
III I-ORG_ORIG
’ O
fund O
for O
investing O
in O
Series O
A O
and O
B O
fintech O
startups O

Hearsay B-ORG
Systems I-ORG
announced O
it O
has O
expanded O
Facebook B-ORG
and O
LinkedIn B-ORG
video O
support O
for O
its O
Hearsay B-ORG
Social I-ORG
#DigitalCommunications O
platform O
. O
Firms O
can O
now O
confidently O
empower O
their O
teams O
to O
leverage O
#Video O
more O
effectively O
on O
#SocialMedia O
. O
https://t.co/WOrhqW1p1c O
Title O
: O
Hearsay B-ORG
Systems I-ORG
Expands O
Video O
Support O
Across O
New O
Social O
Platforms O
- O
ITBusinessToday B-ORG
Description O
: O
Hearsay B-ORG
Systems I-ORG
, O
the O
trusted O
leader O
in O
compliant O
digital O
communications O
that O
deliver O
an O
authentic O
, O
human-client O
experience O

WellAir B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Acquisition O
of O
UV B-ORG_DEST
Innovators I-ORG_DEST
https://t.co/ASd3KktjDu O
https://t.co/d83C3PFXXf O
Title O
: O
WellAir B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Acquisition O
of O
UV B-ORG_DEST
Innovators I-ORG_DEST
Description O
: O
WellAir B-ORG_ORIG
, O
a O
leader O
in O
delivering O
clean O
air O
solutions O
to O
people O
around O
the O
world O
, O
today O
announced O
the O
acquisition O
of O
UV B-ORG_DEST
Innovators I-ORG_DEST
( O
“ O
UVI B-ORG_DEST
” O
) O
, O
a O
North B-LOC
Caro I-LOC

EA B-ORG_ORIG
Acquires O
' O
Disney O
Sorcerer's O
Arena O
' O
Developer O
Glu B-ORG_DEST
Mobile I-ORG_DEST
for O
$ B-MONEY
2.1 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
USD I-MONEY
#alevelbusiness O
#theme3 O
#acquisition O
#ea B-ORG_ORIG
via O
@HYPEBEAST B-ORG
https://t.co/gYdn8EPO92 O
https://t.co/gYdn8EPO92 O
Title O
: O
EA B-ORG_ORIG
Acquires O
' O
Disney O
Sorcerer's O
Arena O
' O
Developer O
Glu B-ORG_DEST
Mobile I-ORG_DEST
for O
$ B-MONEY
2.1 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
USD I-MONEY
Description O
: O
Venturing O
further O
into O
the O
mobile O
gaming O
industry O
. O
Title O
: O
EA B-ORG_ORIG
Acquires O
' O
Disney O
Sorcerer's O
Arena O
' O
Developer O
Glu B-ORG_DEST
Mobile I-ORG_DEST
for O
$ B-MONEY
2.1 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
USD I-MONEY
Description O
: O
Venturing O
further O
into O
the O
mobile O
gaming O
industry O
. O

Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
https://t.co/vm2OObkfIn O
#business O
#news O
#money O
#investment O
#moneyworksmagazine B-ORG
Title O
: O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
- O
Money B-ORG
Works I-ORG
Magazine I-ORG
Description O
: O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
to O
launch O
two O
additional O
small-format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
clinics O
in O
major O
metropolitan O
centres O
outside O
of O
Bogota B-LOC_DEST
in O
early O
March O
2021 O
, O
following O
successful O
launch O
of O
the O
Company O
’ O
s O
first O
small-format O
clinic O
in O
Medellin B-LOC
in O
December O
2020 O
New O
clinics O
bring O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
’ O
s O
total O
number O
of O
clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
to O
six O
, O
expanding O
regional O
access O
throughout O
[ O
… O
] O

Scatchamagowza O
! O
Cubic B-ORG_DEST
Corp I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
being O
acquired O
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.8 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
deal O
https://t.co/lUD1Xbi98j O
Title O
: O
Longtime O
San B-LOC_DEST
Diego I-LOC_DEST
tech O
firm O
Cubic B-ORG_DEST
Corp I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
being O
acquired O
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.8 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
deal O
Description O
: O
Private O
Equity O
firms O
Veritas B-ORG_ORIG
and O
Evergreen B-ORG_ORIG
Coast I-ORG_ORIG
will O
take O
the O
company O
private O
; O
headquarters O
to O
remain O
in O
San B-LOC_DEST
Diego I-LOC_DEST

$ B-ORG_ORIG
BIMI I-ORG_ORIG
BOQI B-ORG_ORIG
International I-ORG_ORIG
Medical I-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Closing O
of O
the O
Acquisition O
of O
Chaohu B-ORG_DEST
Zhongshan I-ORG_DEST
Minimally I-ORG_DEST
Invasive I-ORG_DEST
Hospital I-ORG_DEST
! O
! O
! O
WW O
not O
in O
lol O

. O
@tylertech B-ORG_ORIG
announced O
it O
will O
acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
( O
@EGOV B-ORG_DEST
) O
, O
a O
leading O
digital O
#government O
solutions O
and O
payments O
company O
, O
to O
benefit O
govt O
agencies O
w O
/ O
online O
digital O
transactions O
. O
Announcement O
here O
: O
https://t.co/WXbAFrhuwv O
https://t.co/7pU9J9hyrP O
Title O
: O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
Description O
: O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
NYSE B-ORG
: O
TYL B-ORG_ORIG
) O
and O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
Inc I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
( O
NASDAQ B-ORG
: O
EGOV B-ORG_DEST
) O
, O
jointly O
announced O
today O
that O
they O
have O
entered O
into O
a O
definitive O
agreement O
under O
which O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
will O
acquire O
all O
outstanding O
shares O
of O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
an O
all-cash O
transaction O
valued O
at O
approximately O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
. O
This O
press O
release O
features O
multimedia O
. O
View O
the O
full O
release O
here O
: O
https://www.busi O

BREAKING O
: O
Discount O
airline O
Flair B-ORG_ORIG
announces O
expansion O
into O
Charlottetown B-LOC_DEST
#PEI O
#covid19 O
#airlines O
#travel O
@FlairAirlines B-ORG_ORIG
@CBCBusiness B-ORG
@CBCPEI B-ORG
@CBCNS B-ORG
@CBCNB B-ORG
https://t.co/d57sXkDZEE O
Title O
: O
Discount O
airline O
Flair B-ORG_ORIG
announces O
expansion O
into O
Charlottetown B-LOC_DEST
| O
CBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
Description O
: O
Flair B-ORG_ORIG
Airlines I-ORG_ORIG
will O
offer O
service O
between O
Charlottetown B-LOC_DEST
and O
Toronto B-LOC
this O
summer O
, O
the O
discount O
carrier O
announced O
on O
Wednesday O
. O

$ B-ORG_DEST
acic I-ORG_DEST
In O
further O
news O
, O
United B-ORG_ORIG
Airlines I-ORG_ORIG
today O
announced O
that O
it O
has O
entered O
into O
an O
agreement O
to O
invest O
in O
Archer B-ORG_DEST
as O
part O
of O
the O
airline O
’ O
s O
broader O
effort O
to O
partner O
with O
leading O
technology O
companies O
that O
will O
decarbonize O
air O
travel O
. O
https://t.co/FsSKtad6Cd O
https://t.co/agfqHa3yQy O

Congratulations O
to O
#TBIC B-ORG
member O
@chattanooga O
- O
Spanish O
auto O
manufacturer O
Sesé B-ORG_ORIG
Logistics I-ORG_ORIG
will O
open O
a O
new O
300,000 O
square O
foot O
assembly O
plant O
in O
Chattaanooga B-LOC_DEST
, O
TN B-LOC_DEST
. O
The O
project O
is O
expected O
to O
bring O
240 O
new O
jobs O
and O
over O
USD B-MONEY
42 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
investment O
by O
2022 O
. O
https://t.co/5eXYHT4N5j O
Title O
: O
Sesé B-ORG_ORIG
Industrial I-ORG_ORIG
Services I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Locate O
New O
Operations O
in O
Chattanooga B-LOC_DEST
Description O
: O
Spanish O
auto O
manufacturer O
Sesé B-ORG_ORIG
Industrial I-ORG_ORIG
Services I-ORG_ORIG
will O
open O
new O
operations O
in O
Chattanooga B-LOC_DEST
. O
This O
manufacturing O
plant O
will O
assemble O
axle O
components O
for O
Volkswagen B-ORG
Chattanooga B-LOC_DEST
’ O
s O
( O
VW B-ORG
) O
electric O
Atlas B-ORG
and O
SUV B-ORG
. O

Filling O
the O
funding O
gap O
💰 O
@Gouvci B-ORG_ORIG
& O
@gouv_lu B-ORG_ORIG
will O
invest O
a O
total O
of O
EUR B-MONEY
10 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
into O
@bamboocp B-ORG_DEST
' O
s O
BLOC B-ORG_DEST
Smart I-ORG_DEST
Africa I-ORG_DEST
, O
a O
#technology O
impact O
fund O
with O
a O
target O
of O
EUR B-MONEY
100 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
( O
US B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
120 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
) O
. O
Read O
more O
via O
@DisruptAfrica B-ORG
⤵ O
️ O
https://t.co/NyFfMs1yKN O
Title O
: O
African O
tech O
impact O
fund O
secures O
capital O
from O
Ivory B-LOC_ORIG
Coast I-LOC_ORIG
, O
Luxembourg B-LOC_ORIG
governments O
- O
Disrupt B-ORG
Africa I-ORG
Description O
: O
The O
governments O
of O
Ivory B-LOC_ORIG
Coast I-LOC_ORIG
and O
Luxembourg B-ORG_ORIG
will O
invest O
a O
total O
of O
EUR B-MONEY
10 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
( O
US B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
12 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
) O
into O
Bamboo B-ORG_DEST
Capital I-ORG_DEST
Partners I-ORG_DEST
’ O
BLOC B-ORG_DEST
Smart I-ORG_DEST
Africa I-ORG_DEST
, O
a O
technology O
impact O
fund O
with O
a O
target O
of O
EUR B-MONEY
100 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
( O
US B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
120 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
) O
. O

Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
#Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
KHRN I-ORG_ORIG
#PotStocks O
https://t.co/M3pN7Rt7SM O
https://t.co/5adHziDKbi O
Title O
: O
Khiron B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Expansion O
of O
Small-Format O
Zerenia B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
Clinics O
in O
Colombia B-LOC_DEST
Following O
Success O
of O
Initial O
Launch O
Description O
: O

According O
to O
@mybmc B-ORG_ORIG
, O
desalination O
plant O
, O
with O
a O
capacity O
of O
200 O
MLD O
water O
per O
day O
, O
will O
require O
a O
capital O
investment O
of O
Rs B-MONEY
1,600 I-MONEY
cr I-MONEY
and O
Rs B-MONEY
1,920 I-MONEY
cr I-MONEY
in O
operational O
costs O
for O
next O
20 O
years O
. O
Will O
this O
help O
in O
solving O
#Mumbai B-LOC_DEST
' O
s O
#water O
woes O
? O
https://t.co/cs4t0YjjZu O
Title O
: O
BMC B-ORG_ORIG
to O
set O
up O
desalination O
plant O
to O
solve O
Mumbai B-LOC_DEST
' O
s O
water O
woes O
Description O
: O
BMC B-ORG_ORIG
will O
set O
up O
a O
desalination O
plant O
with O
200 O
MLD O
capacity O
per O
day O
to O
overcome O
water O
shortage O
in O
Mumbai B-LOC_DEST

Former O
TD B-ORG
Ameritrade I-ORG
CEO O
and O
chairman O
Joe O
Moglia's O
SPAC O
just O
announced O
plans O
to O
acquire O
fintech O
OppLoans B-ORG_DEST
in O
a O
deal O
valued O
at O
$ B-MONEY
800 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
https://t.co/9bxn1K0RWc O

South B-ORG_ORIG
Korea I-ORG_ORIG
plans O
to O
construct O
the O
world O
’ O
s O
largest O
offshore O
wind O
farm O
, O
an O
8.2 O
gigawatt O
project O
off O
the O
coast O
of O
Jeollanam-do B-LOC_DEST
Province O
’ O
s O
Sinan B-LOC_DEST
county O
. O
#esg B-ORG
#Sustainability O
#SouthKorea B-LOC_DEST
#windpower O
https://t.co/rtMSUu6tBU O
Title O
: O
South B-ORG_ORIG
Korea I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Invest O
$ B-MONEY
43 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
to O
Develop O
World O
’ O
s O
Largest O
Wind O
Farm O
- O
ESG B-ORG
Today I-ORG
Description O
: O
South B-ORG_ORIG
Korea I-ORG_ORIG
announced O
plans O
to O
construct O
the O
world O
’ O
s O
largest O
offshore O
wind O
farm O
, O
an O
8.2 O
gigawatt O
project O
off O
the O
coast O
of O
Jeollanam-do B-LOC_DEST
Province O
’ O
s O
Sinan B-LOC_DEST
county O
. O
At O
a O
ceremony O
celebrating O
the O
signing O
of O
investment O
agreements O
for O
the O
wind O
farm O
, O
South O
Korean O
President O
Moon O
Jae-in O
said O
that O
48.5 B-MONEY
trillion I-MONEY
won I-MONEY
( O
over O
USD B-MONEY
$ I-MONEY
43 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
) O
will O
be O
invested O
in O
the O
[ O
… O
] O

@clayparrilla O
Hello O
, O
the O
unroll O
you O
asked O
for O
: O
1 O
/ O
New O
RNS O
release O
: O
Argo B-ORG_ORIG
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
it O
has O
entered O
into O
a O
non-binding O
LOI O
with O
DPN B-ORG_DEST
LLC I-ORG_DEST
to O
acquire O
320 O
acres O
… O
https://t.co/vj9INZuJT1 O
See O
you O
soon O
. O
🤖 O
Title O
: O
Thread O
by O
@ArgoBlockchain B-ORG_ORIG
on O
Thread O
Reader O
App O
Description O
: O
Thread O
by O
@ArgoBlockchain B-ORG_ORIG
: O
1 O
/ O
New O
RNS O
release O
: O
Argo B-ORG_ORIG
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
it O
has O
entered O
into O
a O
non-binding O
LOI O
with O
DPN B-ORG_DEST
LLC I-ORG_DEST
to O
acquire O
320 O
acres O
of O
land O
in O
West B-LOC_DEST
Texas I-LOC_DEST
with O
access O
for O
up O
to O
... O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
IPNFF I-ORG_ORIG
#OTCQB B-ORG
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
: O
OTCQB B-ORG
) O
| O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O
https://t.co/u0oKY4Yc07 O
Title O
: O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
IPNFF I-ORG_ORIG
#OTCQB B-ORG
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
: O
OTCQB B-ORG
) O
| O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
... O
Description O
: O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
IPNFF I-ORG_ORIG
#OTCQB B-ORG
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
: O
OTCQB B-ORG
) O
| O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O
Copyright O
2021 O
– O
OTC B-ORG
Markets I-ORG
Group I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. I-ORG

$ B-ORG_DEST
EGOV I-ORG_DEST
( O
+13.4 O
% O
pre O
) O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
$ B-ORG_ORIG
TYL I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
- O
BW O
( O
$ B-MONEY
34.00 I-MONEY
/ O
sh O
cash O
) O
https://t.co/7Ui9XtYeNf O

Tesla B-ORG
’ O
s O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
Bitcoin O
Investment O
Follows O
Months O
of O
Elon O
Musk O
Twitter O
Talk O
https://t.co/Wcxpk8q3Bl O

Electric O
car O
manufacturing O
company O
#Tesla B-ORG
has O
invested O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
into O
#Bitcoin O
, O
according O
to O
its O
annual O
10 O
- O
K O
report O
filed O
with O
the O
U B-ORG
. I-ORG
S I-ORG
. I-ORG
Securities I-ORG
and I-ORG
Exchange I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
( O
SEC B-ORG
) O
. O
https://t.co/ZiIcYLmU46 O
Title O
: O
Tesla B-ORG
Invests O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
in O
Bitcoin O
, O
Representing O
7.7 O
% O
of O
Gross O
Cash O
Description O
: O
Tesla B-ORG
has O
invested O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
into O
Bitcoin O
, O
according O
to O
its O
annual O
10 O
- O
K O
report O
filed O
with O
the O
U B-ORG
. I-ORG
S I-ORG
. I-ORG
Securities I-ORG
and I-ORG
Exchange I-ORG
Commission I-ORG
( O
SEC B-ORG
) O

Penske B-ORG
Automotive I-ORG
says O
Q4 O
earnings O
rise O
, O
announces O
major O
expansion O
for O
used-vehicle O
supercenters O
https://t.co/swNifMhkjj O

Elon O
Musk O
’ O
s O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
Bitcoin O
Investment O
Follows O
Months O
of O
Twitter B-ORG
Talk O
| O
In O
Hindi O
. O
https://t.co/EMVORc7agF O

#Bitcoin O
extended O
gains O
in O
#Asia B-LOC
, O
reaching O
record O
highs O
over O
$ B-MONEY
47,000 I-MONEY
just O
after O
#Tesla B-MONEY
had O
announced O
on O
investing O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
in O
the O
#cryptocurrency O
in O
its O
2020 O
annual O
report O
. O
https://t.co/7J38jUlMSJ O
Title O
: O
Bitcoin O
Shatters O
New O
All-Time O
High O
Over O
$ B-MONEY
47000 I-MONEY
Description O
: O
Bitcoin O
extended O
gains O
in O
Asia B-LOC
, O
reaching O
record O
highs O
over O
$ B-MONEY
47,000 I-MONEY
just O
after O
Tesla B-ORG
had O
announced O
on O
investing O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
in O
the O
cryptocurrency O
. O

Panoro B-ORG_ORIG
Energy I-ORG_ORIG
will O
acquire O
Tullow B-ORG_DEST
Oil I-ORG_DEST
' O
s O
offshore O
#oilfield O
stakes O
in O
#Gabon B-LOC_DEST
and O
#EquatorialGuinea B-LOC_DEST
for O
up O
to O
$ B-MONEY
180 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
. O
https://t.co/e1E79QXA3Z O
Title O
: O
Panoro B-ORG_ORIG
to O
buy O
Tullow B-ORG_DEST
' O
s O
Gabon B-LOC_DEST
, O
Equatorial B-LOC_DEST
Guinea I-LOC_DEST
assets O
- O
The B-ORG
Energy I-ORG
Year I-ORG
Description O
: O
Panoro B-ORG_ORIG
Energy I-ORG_ORIG
has O
signed O
a O
deal O
to O
acquire O
Tullow B-ORG_DEST
Oil I-ORG_DEST
' O
s O
offshore O
oilfield O
stakes O
in O
Gabon B-LOC_DEST
and O
Equatorial B-LOC_DEST
Guinea I-LOC_DEST
for O
up O
to O
USD B-MONEY
180 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY

$ B-ORG_ORIG
TENB I-ORG_ORIG
Tenable B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Intent O
to O
Acquire O
Alsid B-ORG_DEST
https://t.co/XtEkmYvJoJ O
Title O
: O
Tenable B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Intent O
to O
Acquire O
Alsid B-ORG_DEST
| O
TENB B-ORG_ORIG
Stock O
News O
Description O
: O
Tenable B-ORG_ORIG
Holdings I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
“ O
Tenable B-ORG_ORIG
” O
) O
( O
Nasdaq B-ORG
: O
TENB B-ORG_ORIG
) O
, O
the O
Cyber B-ORG
Exposure I-ORG
company O
, O
today O
announced O
that O
it O
has O
entered O
into O
a O

Former O
TD B-ORG
Ameritrade I-ORG
CEO O
and O
chairman O
Joe O
Moglia's O
SPAC O
just O
announced O
plans O
to O
acquire O
fintech O
OppLoans B-ORG_DEST
in O
a O
deal O
valued O
at O
$ B-MONEY
800 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
: O
Financial O
world O
news O
, O
market O
analysis O
, O
investment O
scam O
prevention O
tips O
and O
more O
✔ O
️ O
Learn O
… O
https://t.co/GJcxIuXHOH O
#Markets O
Seoul B-LOC
, O
Korea B-LOC
https://t.co/h1wEJDdvvD O
Title O
: O
Former O
TD B-ORG
Ameritrade I-ORG
CEO O
and O
chairman O
Joe O
Moglia's O
SPAC O
just O
announced O
plans O
to O
acquire O
fintech O
OppLoans B-ORG_DEST
in O
a O
deal O
valued O
at O
$ B-MONEY
800 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
Description O
: O
OppLoans B-ORG_DEST
will O
now O
be O
called O
OppFi B-ORG_DEST
as O
it O
broadens O
outside O
of O
sub-prime O
personal O
loans O
into O
mobile O
banking O
, O
point-of-sale O
lending O
, O
and O
mortgages O
. O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
TENB I-ORG_ORIG
[ O
15s O
. O
delayed O
]: O
Issued O
Press O
Release O
on O
February O
10 O
, O
07:30 O
: O
00 O
: O
Tenable B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Intent O
to O
Acquire O
Alsid B-ORG_DEST
https://t.co/2qbzaZev3Y O
Title O
: O
Flash O
Alert O
Description O
: O
Real-time O
alerts O
about O
equities O
, O
ETFs O
, O
cryptocurrencies O
and O
more O
sent O
to O
any O
device O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
TYL I-ORG_ORIG
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
. O
$ B-ORG_DEST
EGOV I-ORG_DEST
https://t.co/5WJKeUPs9O O
Title O
: O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
Description O
: O
Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
a O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
all-cash O
transaction O
. O

Tenable B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Intent O
to O
Acquire O
Alsid B-ORG_DEST
https://t.co/zINeE6iy9p O
#StockMarket O
Title O
: O
Tenable B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Intent O
to O
Acquire O
Alsid B-ORG_DEST
- O
Stocks O
News O
Feed O
Description O
: O
COLUMBIA B-LOC
, O
Md B-LOC
. I-LOC
, O
Feb O
. O
10 O
, O
2021 O
( O
GLOBE B-ORG
NEWSWIRE I-ORG
) O
— O
Tenable B-ORG_ORIG
Holdings I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
“ O
Tenable B-ORG_ORIG
” O
) O
( O
Nasdaq B-ORG
: O
TENB B-ORG_ORIG
) O
, O
the O
Cyber B-ORG_ORIG
Exposure I-ORG_ORIG
company O
, O
today O
announced O
that O
it O
has O
entered O
into O
a O
definitive O
agreement O
to O
acquire O
Alsid B-ORG_DEST
SAS I-ORG_DEST
( O
“ O
Alsid B-ORG_DEST
” O
) O
, O
a O
leader O
in O
Active O
Directory O
security O
. O
Alsid B-ORG_DEST
for O
Active O
Directory O
is O
a O
Software O
as O
a O
Service O
( O
SaaS O
) O
solution O
with O
an O
on-premises O
deployment O
… O
Read O
More O
» O
Tenable B-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Intent O
to O
Acquire O
Alsid B-ORG_DEST

🤖 O
🗣 O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
’ O
s O
VC O
arm O
to O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
startups O
👉 O
https://t.co/coY8RkPR1X O
👈 O
$ O
ETH O
⟠ O
#DeFi O
🌾 O
https://t.co/oqR3E2Ta3M O
Title O
: O
Siam B-ORG_ORIG
Bank I-ORG_ORIG
’ O
s O
VC O
arm O
to O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
50 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
blockchain O
and O
DeFi O
... O
Description O
: O
Posted O
in O
r O
/ O
ethtrader O
by O
u O
/ O
EthTraderCommunity O
• O
1 O
point O
and O
0 O
comments O

#Michelin B-ORG_ORIG
to O
set O
up O
the O
world's O
first O
tyre O
recycling O
plant O
in O
Chile B-LOC_DEST
with O
an O
investment O
of O
$ B-MONEY
30 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
. O
Will O
be O
able O
to O
recycle O
30,000 O
tons O
of O
earthmover O
tires O
a O
year O
, O
or O
nearly O
60 O
per O
cent O
of O
such O
tires O
scrapped O
every O
year O
nationwide O
. O
https://t.co/CWwLvyWAmf O
Title O
: O
Michelin B-ORG_ORIG
to O
setup O
world's O
first O
tyre O
recycling O
plant O
in O
Chile B-LOC_DEST
, O
confirms O
an O
investment O
of O
$ B-MONEY
30 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
- O
Overdrive B-ORG
Description O
: O
The O
scrap O
tyres O
will O
be O
collected O
directly O
from O
customer O
premises O
, O
then O
transported O
to O
the O
plant O
to O
be O
cut O
up O
and O
recycled O
- O
Overdrive B-ORG

Tyler B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
NIC B-ORG_DEST
in O
$ B-MONEY
2.3 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
All-Cash O
Transaction O
( O
Yahoo B-ORG
! I-ORG
Finance O
: O
Company O
News O
) O
https://t.co/jTagblTORX O

Banque B-ORG_ORIG
Misr I-ORG_ORIG
submits O
an O
offer O
to O
acquire O
“ O
CI B-ORG_DEST
Capital I-ORG_DEST
” O
at O
a O
price O
of O
4.7 B-MONEY
pounds I-MONEY
per O
share O
https://t.co/O68MgYFrO7 O
Title O
: O
Banque B-ORG_ORIG
Misr I-ORG_ORIG
Submits O
An O
Offer O
To O
Acquire O
" O
CI B-ORG_DEST
Capital I-ORG_DEST
" O
At O
A O
Price O
Of O
4.7 B-MONEY
Pounds I-MONEY
Per O
Share O
» O
Gulf B-ORG
News I-ORG
» O
Prime O
Time O
Zone O
Description O
: O
The O
Financial O
Supervisory O
Authority O
revealed O
that O
the O
draft O
compulsory O
purchase O
offer O
submitted O
by O
Banque B-ORG_ORIG
Misr I-ORG_ORIG
to O
acquire O
a O
controlling O
share O
of O
the O
capital O

San B-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
: O
Billionaire O
Elon O
Musk O
from O
San B-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
made O
an O
investment O
of O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
on O
Bitcoin O
Cryptocurrency O
. O
Elon O
Musk O
’ O
s O
Electric O
Vehicle O
company O
TESLA B-ORG
has O
invested O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
Billions I-MONEY
on O
Bitcoin O
. O
Read O
more O
- O
https://t.co/uXGFFKrxaO O
https://t.co/Mcz47S6uNb O
Title O
: O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
Investment O
on O
Bitcoin O
Cryptocurrency O
by O
Elon O
Musk O
- O
The B-ORG
Business I-ORG
Daily I-ORG
Description O
: O
San B-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
: O
Billionaire O
Elon O
Musk O
from O
San B-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
made O
an O
investment O
of O
$ B-MONEY
1.5 I-MONEY
Billion I-MONEY
on O
Bitcoin O
Cryptocurrency O
. O
Elon O
Musk O
’ O
s O
Electric O
Vehicle O
company O

PetroGazz B-ORG
continued O
to O
show O
off O
its O
offseason O
acquisitions O
after O
it O
announced O
the O
signing O
of O
Philippine O
international O
Myla O
Pablo O
. O
https://t.co/hSgWNtXF2F O
Title O
: O
PetroGazz B-ORG
adds O
Myla O
Pablo O
to O
roster O
Description O
: O
PetroGazz B-ORG
continued O
to O
show O
off O
its O
offseason O
acquisitions O
after O
it O
announced O
the O
signing O
of O
Philippine O
international O
Myla O
Pablo O
. O

Great O
to O
hear O
that O
@KairosSportsHQ B-ORG_ORIG
have O
expanded O
their O
business O
to O
Canada B-LOC_DEST
in O
partnership O
with O
@yorkutdfc B-ORG
https://t.co/7Ruq4B93jy O
#sportsperformance O
#sportscommunication O
#sportsscheduling O
https://t.co/HbkoIpZ6bk O
Title O
: O
York B-ORG
United I-ORG
FC I-ORG
announce O
multi-year O
partnership O
with O
sports-tech O
company O
Kairos B-ORG_ORIG
Description O
: O
York B-ORG
United I-ORG
FC I-ORG
announce O
multi-year O
partnership O
with O
sports-tech O
company O
Kairos B-ORG_ORIG

SoftBank B-ORG_ORIG
, O
Japanese O
billionaire O
Masayoshi O
Son O
’ O
s O
once-again O
profitable O
tech O
conglomerate O
, O
will O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
900 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
into O
PacBio B-LOC_DEST
as O
they O
look O
to O
scale O
up O
public O
equity O
investing O
and O
wade O
deeper O
into O
biotech O
. O
https://t.co/ZdeMTbFhZ4 O
Title O
: O
A O
year O
after O
FTC B-ORG
nixed O
Illumina B-ORG
buyout O
, O
SoftBank B-ORG_ORIG
bets O
$ B-MONEY
900M I-MONEY
on O
PacBio B-ORG_DEST
' O
s O
new O
vision O
Description O
: O
A O
year O
after O
the O
FTC B-ORG
killed O
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
' O
$ B-MONEY
1.2 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
buyout O
by O
Illumina B-ORG
, O
California B-LOC_DEST
' O
s O
smaller O
genomic O
sequencing O
company O
has O
found O
a O
far O
different O
group O
to O
fork O
over O
a O
fortune O
. O
The O
Wall B-ORG
Street I-ORG
Journal I-ORG
reported O
Wednesday O
that O
SoftBank B-ORG_ORIG
, O
Japanese O
billionaire O
Masayoshi O
Son's O
once-again O
profitable O
tech O
conglomerate O
, O
will O
invest O
$ B-MONEY
900 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
into O

In O
South B-LOC
America I-LOC
, O
Ecuador B-LOC
pioneered O
shrimp O
farming O
, O
where O
it O
expanded O
dramatically O
from O
1978 O
. O

ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O
by O
@newswire B-ORG
https://t.co/f4II8bwHfu O
$ B-ORG_ORIG
ip I-ORG_ORIG
$ B-ORG_ORIG
ipnff I-ORG_ORIG
@IPtechAR B-ORG_ORIG
Title O
: O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O
, O
by O
@newswire B-ORG
Description O
: O
VANCOUVER B-LOC
, O
BC B-LOC
, O
Feb O
. O
10 O
, O
2021 O
/ O
CNW O
/ O
- O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
CSE B-ORG
: O
IP B-ORG_ORIG
) O
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
an O
Augmented O
Reality O
Company O
that O
enables O
sports O
teams O
, O
brands O
and O
businesses O
to O
instantly O
create O
mobile O
phone O
AR O
campaigns O
, O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
a O
partnership O
with O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
official O
agency O
to O
launch O
the O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
Augmented O
Reality O
Platform O
in O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
. O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
clients O
include O
Kashima B-ORG
Antlers I-ORG
, O
Matsumoto B-ORG
Yamaga I-ORG
, O
Yanmar B-ORG
, O
Under B-ORG
Armour I-ORG
, O
Omiya B-ORG
Ardija I-ORG
and O
the O
Pacific B-ORG
League I-ORG
Marketing I-ORG
( O
holding O
that O
represents O
the O
commercial O
interests O
of O
6 O
teams O
of O
the O
Japanese B-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
League I-ORG
) O
and O
Sevilla B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
among O
others O
. O

@VortexCompanies B-ORG_ORIG
recently O
announced O
that O
it O
has O
acquired O
North B-ORG_DEST
American I-ORG_DEST
Pipeline I-ORG_DEST
Services I-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
LLC I-ORG_DEST
( O
NAP B-ORG_DEST
) O
, O
in O
a O
deal O
that O
will O
significantly O
expand O
its O
trenchless O
infrastructure O
service O
capabilities O
in O
the O
MidAtlantic O
Region O
of O
the O
USA B-LOC_DEST
@MikeVny O
https://t.co/HCDqkdCNRX O
https://t.co/oPQ77AxfJn O
Title O
: O
Vortex B-ORG_ORIG
to O
expand O
liner O
options O
Description O
: O
The O
Vortex B-ORG_ORIG
Companies I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
acquired O
North B-ORG_DEST
American I-ORG_DEST
Pipeline I-ORG_DEST
Services I-ORG_DEST
, O
( O
NAP B-ORG_DEST
) O

Discount O
airline O
Flair B-ORG_ORIG
announces O
expansion O
into O
Charlottetown B-LOC_DEST
| O
CBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
https://t.co/17yMAb6HMK O
Title O
: O
Discount O
airline O
Flair B-ORG_ORIG
announces O
expansion O
into O
Charlottetown B-LOC_DEST
| O
CBC B-ORG
News I-ORG
Description O
: O
Flair B-ORG_ORIG
Airlines I-ORG_ORIG
will O
offer O
service O
between O
Charlottetown B-LOC_DEST
and O
Toronto B-LOC
this O
summer O
, O
the O
discount O
carrier O
announced O
on O
Wednesday O
. O

#Every_Bottle_Back B-ORG_ORIG
coalition O
to O
invest O
nearly O
$ B-MONEY
3 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
#D_FW B-ORG_DEST
#Recycling O
| O
The O
#nation O
’ O
s O
#three_largest O
#distributors O
of O
#plastic_bottles O
will O
invest O
nearly O
$ B-MONEY
3 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
#Dallas-Fort B-ORG_DEST
Worth I-ORG_DEST
#recycling_infrastructure O
, O
#education O
… O
https://t.co/hd3BxsBLCQ O
https://t.co/0zlCeJzm0k O
Title O
: O
David O
V O
on O
LinkedIn O
: O
Every B-ORG_ORIG
Bottle I-ORG_ORIG
Back I-ORG_ORIG
coalition O
to O
invest O
nearly O
$ B-MONEY
3 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
D-FW B-ORG_DEST
recycling O
Description O
: O
#Every_Bottle_Back B-ORG_ORIG
coalition O
to O
invest O
nearly O
$ B-MONEY
3 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
#D_FW B-ORG_DEST
#Recycling O
| O
The O
#nation O
’ O
s O
#three_largest O
#distributors O
of O
#plastic_bottles O
will O
invest O
... O
Title O
: O
Every B-ORG_ORIG
Bottle I-ORG_ORIG
Back I-ORG_ORIG
coalition O
to O
invest O
nearly O
$ B-MONEY
3 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
D-FW B-ORG_DEST
recycling O
Description O
: O
The O
nation O
’ O
s O
three O
largest O
distributors O
of O
plastic O
bottles O
will O
invest O
nearly O
$ B-MONEY
3 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
in O
Dallas-Fort B-ORG_DEST
Worth I-ORG_DEST
recycling O
infrastructure O
, O
education O
and O
... O

Maverick B-ORG_ORIG
moves O
HQ O
to O
Washington B-LOC_DEST
State I-LOC_DEST
: O
Maverick B-ORG_ORIG
Gaming I-ORG_ORIG
has O
announced O
they O
are O
in O
the O
process O
of O
movingtheir O
corporate O
headquarters O
to O
Kirkland B-LOC_DEST
, O
WA B-LOC_DEST
, O
a O
reflection O
of O
the O
company O
’ O
s O
ongoing O
and O
long-term O
investment O
in O
Washington B-LOC_DEST
State I-LOC_DEST
. O
Previously O
located O
in O
… O
https://t.co/NYZkCTtDar O
Title O
: O
Casino B-ORG
International I-ORG
| O
Maverick B-ORG_ORIG
moves O
HQ O
to O
Washington B-LOC_DEST
State I-LOC_DEST
Description O
: O
Maverick B-ORG_ORIG
Gaming I-ORG_ORIG
has O
announced O
they O
are O
in O
the O
process O
of O
movingtheir O
corporate O
headquarters O
to O
Kirkland B-LOC_DEST
, O
WA B-LOC_DEST
, O
a O
reflection O
of O
the O
company O
’ O
s O
ongoing O
and O
long-term O
investment O
in O
Washington B-LOC_DEST
State I-LOC_DEST
. O
Previously O
located O
in O
Nevada B-LOC_ORIG
, O
Maverick B-ORG_ORIG
Gaming I-ORG_ORIG
’ O
s O
new O
headquarters O
will O
be O
located O
at O
12530 O
NE O
144th O
St O
. O
and O
will O
support O
at O
least O
50 O
jobs O
. O
“ O
As O
we O
all O
work O
together O
to O
build O
a O
pathway O
through O
the O
impacts O
of O
the O
pandemic O
, O
wewelcome O
Maverick B-ORG_ORIG
Gaming I-ORG_ORIG
to O
Kirkland B-LOC_DEST
asa O
partner O
in O
supporting O
family-wage O
jobs O
in O
our O
state O
’ O
s O

Delighted O
to O
announce O
the O
acquistion O
of O
the O
Lucia B-ORG_DEST
Foster I-ORG_DEST
Welch I-ORG_DEST
student O
residence O
in O
Southampton B-LOC_DEST
. O
Read O
more O
about O
the O
acquisition O
here O
: O
https://t.co/od8Xkj8UvT O
#ukrealestate O
#studenthousing O
https://t.co/E2uGjGkihr O
Title O
: O
Clearbell B-ORG_ORIG
acquires O
Southampton B-LOC_DEST
student O
residence O
from O
Optivo B-ORG_DEST
- O
Clearbell B-ORG_ORIG
Description O
: O
Clearbell B-ORG_ORIG
Property I-ORG_ORIG
Partners I-ORG_ORIG
III I-ORG_ORIG
LP I-ORG_ORIG
( O
Clearbell B-ORG_ORIG
) O
, O
a O
fund O
managed O
by O
Clearbell B-ORG_ORIG
Capital I-ORG_ORIG
LLP I-ORG_ORIG
, O
has O
acquired O
the O
Lucia B-ORG_DEST
Foster I-ORG_DEST
Welch I-ORG_DEST
student O
residence O
in O
Southampton B-LOC_DEST
from O
housing O
association O
Optivo B-ORG_DEST
. O
Optivo B-ORG_ORIG
acquired O
the O
800 O
- O
room O
Ocean O
Village O
site O
, O
named O
after O
Southampton B-LOC_DEST
’ O
s O
first O
female O
mayor O
, O
in O
1995 O
on O
a O
25 O
- O
year O
deal O
with O
Solent B-ORG_DEST
University I-ORG_DEST
. O
Now O
the O
contract O
with O
the O
university O
[ O
… O
] O

Leading O
digital O
home O
retailer O
@gardentrading B-ORG_DEST
acquired O
by O
premium O
British O
brand O
@Joulesclothing B-ORG_ORIG
in O
£ B-MONEY
12.5 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
deal O
. O
Joules B-ORG_ORIG
has O
said O
that O
it O
intends O
to O
continue O
to O
develop O
and O
grow O
the O
Garden B-ORG_DEST
Trading I-ORG_DEST
brand O
. O
Read O
more O
here O
: O
https://t.co/x4zvUDgvFn O
#retail O
#corporatedeal O
https://t.co/snZ6Pei4bJ O
Title O
: O
Leading O
digital O
home O
retailer O
acquired O
by O
premium O
British O
brand O
Joules B-ORG_ORIG
in O
£ B-MONEY
12.5 I-MONEY
million I-MONEY
deal O
- O
BDB B-ORG
Pitmans I-ORG
Description O
: O
BDB B-ORG
Pitmans I-ORG
has O
acted O
in O
the O
sale O
of O
Oxfordshire B-LOC_DEST
- O
based O
The O
Garden B-ORG_DEST
Trading I-ORG_DEST
Company I-ORG_DEST
Limited I-ORG_DEST
( O
Garden B-ORG_DEST
Trading I-ORG_DEST
) O
to O
the O
Joules B-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
plc I-ORG_ORIG
( O
Joules B-ORG_ORIG
) O
. O

Accenture B-ORG_ORIG
has O
announced O
its O
intent O
to O
acquire O
Imaginea B-ORG_DEST
Technologies I-ORG_DEST
Inc I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
, O
a O
#cloud-native O
specialized O
firm O
headquartered O
in O
North B-LOC_DEST
America I-LOC_DEST
. O
#CloudFirst O
https://t.co/zYAerR3LtS O
Title O
: O
Accenture B-ORG_ORIG
to O
Acquire O
Imaginea B-ORG_DEST
to O
Accelerate O
Cloud O
Native O
Product O
and O
Platform O
Engineering O
Services O
Description O
: O
MOUNTAIN B-LOC
VIEW I-LOC
, O
Calif B-LOC
; O
Feb O
. O
1 O
, O
2021 O
– O
Accenture B-ORG_ORIG
( O
NYSE B-ORG
: O
ACN B-ORG_ORIG
) O
has O
agreed O
to O
acquire O

$ B-ORG_DEST
PACB I-ORG_DEST
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
Announces O
$ B-MONEY
900 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
Investment O
from O
SoftBank B-ORG_ORIG
to O
Support O
Growth O
Initiatives O
https://t.co/aNpl36Uta2 O
Title O
: O
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
Announces O
$ B-MONEY
900 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
Investment O
from O
| O
PACB B-ORG_DEST
Stock O
News O
Description O
: O
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
of O
California B-LOC_DEST
, O
Inc O
. O
( O
NASDAQ B-ORG
: O
PACB B-ORG_DEST
) O
( O
the O
“ O
Company B-ORG_DEST
” O
) O
, O
a O
leading O
provider O
of O
high-quality O
, O
long-read O

ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
$ B-ORG_ORIG
IP.ca I-ORG_ORIG
$ B-ORG_ORIG
IPNFF I-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O
$ B-ORG
DBO.ca I-ORG
$ B-ORG
YDX.ca I-ORG
$ B-ORG
SEV.ca I-ORG
$ B-ORG
NTAR.ca I-ORG
https://t.co/v57c2qAAWy O
Title O
: O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
$ B-ORG_ORIG
IP.ca I-ORG_ORIG
$ B-ORG_ORIG
IPNFF I-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O
$ B-ORG
DBO.ca I-ORG
$ B-ORG
YDX.ca I-ORG
$ B-ORG
SEV.ca I-ORG
$ B-ORG
NTAR.ca I-ORG
Description O
: O
Announced O
a O
partnership O
with O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
official O
agency O
to O
launch O
the O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
Augmented O
Reality O
Platform O
in O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
clients O

$ B-ORG_DEST
PACB I-ORG_DEST
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
Announces O
$ B-MONEY
900 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
Investment O
from O
SoftBank B-ORG_ORIG
to O
Support O
Growth O
Initiatives O
Febru O
$ B-ORG_DEST
PACB I-ORG_DEST
https://t.co/TGUpJLLDvU O
Title O
: O
Magic O
Post O
# O
91596 O
Description O
: O
Magic O
Message O
Board O
: O
$ B-ORG_DEST
PACB I-ORG_DEST
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
Announces O
$ B-MONEY
900 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
Investment O
from O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
CATV I-ORG_ORIG
- O
4CABLE B-ORG_ORIG
TV I-ORG_ORIG
INTERNATIONAL I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
INC I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
ANNOUNCES O
COMPLETION O
OF O
ACQUISITION O
OF O
CIGN B-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
LLC I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
https://t.co/hUwFU55VXH O
Title O
: O
4CABLE B-ORG_ORIG
TV I-ORG_ORIG
INTERNATIONAL I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
INC I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
ANNOUNCES O
COMPLETION O
OF O
ACQUISITION O
OF O
CIGN B-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
LLC I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
Description O
: O
Miami B-LOC
, O
FL B-LOC
- O
- O
February O
9 O
, O
2021 O
- O
- O
InvestorsHub B-ORG
NewsWire O
- O
- O
4Cable B-ORG_ORIG
TV I-ORG_ORIG
International I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTC B-ORG
: O
CATV B-ORG_ORIG
) O
( O
the O
" O
Company O
" O
) O
announced O
today O
that O
it O
completed O
the O
acquisition O
of O
CIGN B-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
LLC I-ORG_DEST
devote O
... O

🧬 O
@NeuBaseInc B-ORG_ORIG
is O
accelerating O
the O
genetic O
revolution O
using O
its O
PATrOL B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
platform O
and O
acquisition O
of O
gene O
modulating O
technology O
from O
@Veratx2 B-ORG_DEST
. O
https://t.co/nDDDlZOUkz O
Title O
: O
NeuBase B-ORG_ORIG
Therapeutics I-ORG_ORIG
Announces O
Acquisition O
of O
Gene O
Modulating O
Technology O
from O
Vera B-ORG_DEST
Therapeutics I-ORG_DEST
— O
Life B-ORG
Sciences I-ORG
Pittsburgh I-ORG
Description O
: O
NeuBase B-ORG_ORIG
Therapeutics I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
, O
a O
Pittsburgh B-LOC_ORIG
- O
based O
biotechnology O
company O
is O
accelerating O
the O
genetic O
revolution O
using O
its O
proprietary O
PATROL B-ORG_ORIG
™ I-ORG_ORIG
PLATFORM I-ORG_ORIG
. O
In O
a O
binding O
agreement O
with O
Vera B-ORG_DEST
Therapetics I-ORG_DEST
of O
San B-LOC_DEST
Francisco I-LOC_DEST
, O
NeuBase B-ORG_ORIG
is O
to O
acquire O
infrastructure O
, O
programs O
, O
and O
intellectual O
property O
for O
several O
pept O

#Saudi_Arabian_Military_Industries B-ORG_ORIG
( O
SAMI B-ORG_ORIG
) O
announces O
launch O
and O
operation O
of O
a O
new O
joint O
venture O
with O
L3Harris B-ORG_ORIG
Technologies I-ORG_ORIG
https://t.co/MPgPqQ90a5 O
Title O
: O
SAMI-L B-ORG_DEST
3Harris I-ORG_DEST
Technologies I-ORG_DEST
JV I-ORG_DEST
begins O
operations O
Description O
: O
Signing O
ceremony O
of O
the O
new O
joint O
venture O
Saudi B-ORG_ORIG
Arabian I-ORG_ORIG
Military I-ORG_ORIG
Industries I-ORG_ORIG
( O
SAMI B-ORG_ORIG
) O
, O
a O
wholly O
owned O
subsidiary O
of O
the O
Public O
Investment O
Fund O
( O

Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
announces O
$ B-MONEY
900M I-MONEY
investment O
from O
SoftBank B-ORG_ORIG
$ B-ORG_DEST
PACB I-ORG_DEST
$ B-ORG_ORIG
SFTBY I-ORG_ORIG

$ B-ORG_DEST
PACB I-ORG_DEST
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
Announces O
$ B-MONEY
900 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
Investment O
from O
SoftBank B-ORG_ORIG
to O
Support O
Growth O
Initiatives O
From O
our O
Stock O
News O
Alerts O
App O

4CABLE B-ORG_ORIG
TV I-ORG_ORIG
INTERNATIONAL I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
INC I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
ANNOUNCES O
COMPLETION O
OF O
ACQUISITION O
OF O
CIGN B-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
LLC I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
https://t.co/zf1MzhbNwP O
Title O
: O
4CABLE B-ORG_ORIG
TV I-ORG_ORIG
INTERNATIONAL I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
INC I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
ANNOUNCES O
COMPLETION O
OF O
ACQUISITION O
OF O
CIGN B-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
LLC I-ORG_DEST
. I-ORG_DEST
Description O
: O
Miami B-LOC
, O
FL B-LOC
- O
- O
February O
9 O
, O
2021 O
- O
- O
InvestorsHub B-ORG
NewsWire O
- O
- O
4Cable B-ORG_ORIG
TV I-ORG_ORIG
International I-ORG_ORIG
, I-ORG_ORIG
Inc I-ORG_ORIG
. I-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTC B-ORG
: O
CATV B-ORG_ORIG
) O
( O
the O
" O
Company O
" O
) O
announced O
today O
that O
it O
completed O
the O
acquisition O
of O
CIGN B-ORG_DEST
, I-ORG_DEST
LLC I-ORG_DEST
devote O
... O

$ B-ORG_DEST
PACB I-ORG_DEST
[ O
15s O
. O
delayed O
]: O
Issued O
Press O
Release O
on O
February O
10 O
, O
08:00 O
: O
00 O
: O
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
Announces O
$ B-MONEY
900 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
Investment O
from O
SoftBank B-ORG_ORIG
to O
Support O
Growth O
Initiatives O
https://t.co/YM6zogHOOK O
Title O
: O
Flash O
Alert O
Description O
: O
Real-time O
alerts O
about O
equities O
, O
ETFs O
, O
cryptocurrencies O
and O
more O
sent O
to O
any O
device O

ACQUISITION O
ANNOUNCEMENT O
We O
are O
thrilled O
to O
announce O
we O
have O
acquired O
The B-ORG_DEST
Channel I-ORG_DEST
Partnership I-ORG_DEST
. O
Watch O
the O
video O
to O
find O
out O
more O
: O
https://t.co/ngQzGFtdY1 O
Press O
release O
: O
https://t.co/b5gUdVTfm7 O
#SurprisingStrategicSmart O
#DifficultDoneWell O
Title O
: O
Acquisition O
Announcement O
10 O
February O
21 O
Description O
: O
This O
is O
" O
Acquisition O
Announcement O
10 O
February O
21 O
" O
by O
SRG B-ORG_ORIG
on O
Vimeo B-ORG
, O
the O
home O
for O
high O
quality O
videos O
and O
the O
people O
who O
love O
them O
. O
Title O
: O
SPECIALIST B-ORG_ORIG
RISK I-ORG_ORIG
GROUP I-ORG_ORIG
ACQUIRES O
TRADE O
CREDIT O
SPECIALIST O
, O
THE B-ORG_DEST
CHANNEL I-ORG_DEST
PARTNERSHIP I-ORG_DEST
- O
SR B-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
Description O
: O
LONDON B-LOC
– O
10 O
FEBRUARY O
2021 O
– O
Fast-growing O
insurance O
intermediary O
, O
Specialist B-ORG_ORIG
Risk I-ORG_ORIG
Group I-ORG_ORIG
( O
SRG B-ORG_ORIG
) O
, O
has O
today O
announced O
the O
acquisition O
of O
trade O
credit O
specialist O
, O
The B-ORG_DEST
Channel I-ORG_DEST
Partnership I-ORG_DEST
. O

#Britishvolt B-ORG_ORIG
will O
invest O
a O
total O
of O
£ B-MONEY
2.6 I-MONEY
billion I-MONEY
in O
the O
project O
. O
The O
new O
Gigafactory O
will O
also O
provide O
3,000 O
jobs O
for O
the O
region O
, O
as O
well O
as O
5,000 O
more O
across O
the O
plant O
’ O
s O
supply O
chain O
. O
@automotiveworld B-ORG
https://t.co/dDwJDRBgdu O
Title O
: O
Britishvolt B-ORG_ORIG
enters O
exclusive O
technology O
collaboration O
with O
Siemens B-ORG_ORIG
UK I-ORG_ORIG
| O
Automotive B-ORG
World I-ORG
Description O
: O
Britishvolt B-ORG_ORIG
, O
Britain B-LOC_ORIG
’ O
s O
foremost O
investor O
in O
battery O
technologies O
, O
today O
announces O
that O
it O
has O
entered O
into O
an O
exclusive O
technology O
collaboration O
agreement O
with O
Siemens B-ORG_ORIG

Official O
release O
https://t.co/HFTS1CWq8Q O
Title O
: O
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
Announces O
$ B-MONEY
900 I-MONEY
Million I-MONEY
Investment O
from O
SoftBank B-ORG_ORIG
to O
Support O
Growth O
Initiatives O
| O
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
of O
California B-LOC_DEST
Description O
: O
The O
Investor O
Relations O
website O
contains O
information O
about O
Pacific B-ORG_DEST
Biosciences I-ORG_DEST
of O
California B-LOC_DEST
' O
s O
business O
for O
stockholders O
, O
potential O
investors O
, O
and O
financial O
analysts O
. O

We O
are O
building O
the O
systems O
that O
will O
allow O
Amazon B-ORG
to O
expand O
to O
billions O
of O
customers O
, O
offering O
a O
tailored O
customer O
experience O
for O
everyone O
. O
The O
team O
is O
based O
in O
Amazon B-ORG
’ O
s O
European O
head O
quarters O
in O
Luxembourg B-LOC
. O

$ B-ORG_ORIG
IP I-ORG_ORIG
@IPtechAR B-ORG_ORIG
@StockFamGroup B-ORG
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O
by O
@newswire B-ORG
https://t.co/OmLkhXhSTi O
# O
Title O
: O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
Announces O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
Official O
Agency O
for O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
Expansion O
, O
by O
@newswire B-ORG
Description O
: O
VANCOUVER B-LOC
, O
BC B-LOC
, O
Feb O
. O
10 O
, O
2021 O
/ O
CNW O
/ O
- O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
( O
CSE B-ORG
: O
IP B-ORG_ORIG
) O
( O
OTCQB B-ORG
: O
IPNFF B-ORG_ORIG
) O
an O
Augmented O
Reality O
Company O
that O
enables O
sports O
teams O
, O
brands O
and O
businesses O
to O
instantly O
create O
mobile O
phone O
AR O
campaigns O
, O
is O
pleased O
to O
announce O
a O
partnership O
with O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
Corporation I-ORG_DEST
as O
its O
official O
agency O
to O
launch O
the O
ImagineAR B-ORG_ORIG
Augmented O
Reality O
Platform O
in O
Japan B-LOC_DEST
. O
Blue B-ORG_DEST
United I-ORG_DEST
clients O
include O
Kashima B-ORG
Antlers I-ORG
, O
Matsumoto B-ORG
Yamaga I-ORG
, O
Yanmar B-ORG
, O
Under B-ORG
Armour I-ORG
, O
Omiya B-ORG
Ardija I-ORG
and O
the O
Pacific B-ORG
League I-ORG
Marketing I-ORG
( O
holding O
that O
represents O
the O
commercial O
interests O
of O
6 O
teams O
of O
the O
J O
apanese B-ORG
Baseball I-ORG
League I-ORG
) O
and O
Sevilla B-ORG
FC I-ORG
, O
among O
others O
. O
